dorkmo: letsss gooo
knilecrack: wsuppp
lidermaury: lets get it
quickfloor: yu
SkyforgerCFW: HI GUYS
eax_ebx: go go boyz
quickfloor: wuz popping lil george
foxubu: Greetings :)
0xc0ffeee: wuuzzzzzuuuup
NonTrivial778: brooooOOooOo
lidermaury: Tea is ready
funwayz: IMO PogChamp
thomasbakp: geohot what up from Europe
itsimari: borscht
0xc0ffeee: where dem tea and ice cubes at
nudax: oh livestream
bsx1123: yoyo
Purrplecat: He live?
Purrplecat: !discord
erichtp: LUL
bitwoz: Sup geo!
vbhv: hello hello hello
lidermaury: is he playing christmas songs?
0xc0ffeee: legal lean lolwut
r3mote: Hello =)
foxubu: Who's again trying to fill his pockets with money with some shitty drugs? -.-
Santiago_LHC: Good morning George
y0unghercules: Learn zeekscript
mirceau: sup George
nach7vos: george legend!
cod4TV: !uptime
foxubu: ahhhhhhhhhhhhh! allright!
vbhv: ever been to India?
Harm133: Yo
cod4TV: !up
forkdb: Hello hello
mirceau: Sunday Music :p
serohh: Lets do some clojure programming today!!!
forkdb: Am feeling awesome.. how are you doing george
quickfloor: i'm the first person here
knilecrack: yes
knilecrack: everyone else is a bot
noroumchian: what's the name of the song?
NonTrivial778: blasting music
forkdb: Did you have breakfast
johnny_thehobo: idea: pull some pleb from chat and teach him a new programming language?
OnlyB1ade: well hello
cod4TV: @georgehotz this is my first week being a subscriber. can i get a shout out?
st47ik: Hi George! Hi Chat HeyGuys
forkdb: Please tell me how not to be noob
ByForever: is the music on stream or his house
leopp: so what are we doing today?
knilecrack: hi @st47ik
mephisto7777_: @georgehotz legend still alive LUL
Keyeh: KEKW
OnlyB1ade: U gotta save some
OnlyB1ade: yes
snxraven: HEYYYY
Bombapil0t: SeemsGood
NonTrivial778: LUL
Keyeh: that's eminem i'm pretty sure
st47ik: PogChamp
forkdb: Please tell me how not to be noob
K177Music: Y OMEGALUL
knilecrack: coked up from last night
UniversalGeneve: ghotz 2020
Santiago_LHC: I'm sure Kim Jong-un watches this.
johnny_thehobo: bars
mirceau: Rap Philosophy
johnny_thehobo: that was fire
shaymin_fakezz: AngelThump
K177Music: LUL
lasercatboss: its only when we lose everything that we are free to do anything
OnlyB1ade: Grinding
st47ik: Geohot 2020 PogChamp
cod4TV: @georgehotz yeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeh! THANKS!
gustavo17mb: !song
forkdb: Please tell me how not to be noob... please... give some lessons
cod4TV: @forkdb 1
FargioFarmani: this guy is an entertainer²
Ziv0: gotta love post-rock
liqo13: how much of homotopy type theory did u learn? @georgehotz
lidermaury: its tea time
kektobiologist: can you enable bttv emotes?
serohh: Lets do some clojure programming today!!!!!@georgehotz
forkdb: Please tell me how not to be noob.. please.. give some lessons
mirceau: Amma get me some ice tea
callmemod: What do you think about D?
Bitcoin__: Bitcoin__ subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 9 months!
adibaby04: do some golang please
th3_maj0r: Hi George, did you see ksi vs Logan ?
rikvk01: This is the first time i catch one of these live, nice 😎
forkdb: Please tell me how not to be noob.. please.. give some lessons
PhysoTronic: georgehotz what app for meditation did you use on your last stream?
GGBreach: What's he making?
forkdb: @physotronic Headspace
PhysoTronic: thanks forkdb
th3_maj0r: Did you like the pre-japan Logan?
forkdb: Please tell me how not to be noob.. please.. give some lessons
liqo13: how is lean different from coq or agda?
adibaby04: do golang
forkdb: Please
adibaby04: go
adibaby04: lang
st47ik: Lean Theorem Prover Kreygasm
PhysoTronic: we are talking about Logan x.-men or somebody else?
mirceau: Lol
th3_maj0r: yes, him
OnlyB1ade: What is up
forkdb: Please tell me how not to be noob.. please.. give some lessons... please am dying here to know from you!!
Harm133: whos that monkaS
foxubu: Did someone caugh?
Bombapil0t: cmonBruh
burimbushii: best editor ever used
quickfloor: he is sad cuz of logan paul fight
M03x: LULW
foxubu: Alex <3
st47ik: just learn 4Head
aa_ato: NoUnityAnyMore!
Venald: 1. Pick some books 2. ??? 3. Become pro
Ant__K: 4Head
forkdb: Dude ... seriously
NonTrivial778: she is rude
quickfloor: Watch some porn
M03x: "learn".split('r').join('') haHAA
forkdb: Please am dying here
mirceau: she has no heart
st47ik: @forkdb what lessons u need?
whichtom: go read some books
FargioFarmani: whos alex
GGBreach: @NonTrivial778 what did she say?
Venald: To become a pro you must study and do projects
forkdb: Which books?
whichtom: anything but sit in twitch chat
Ant__K: LUL
Venald: forkdb what do you want to do
Venald: it is the first thing you need to know
M03x: @forkdb do side projects imagine any project and work on it
nso1995: dropped an ice cube
forkdb: In python java and js and golang
forkdb: In general
chocblade: thats cause you will never have a girl friend
foxubu: George, what's your opinion about the Cybertruck? :D
st47ik: im a frozen raindrop
quickfloor: Apply for google intership then u will be pro
mirceau: Watch Jordan Peterson, he’ll teach you how to not be n00b.
forkdb: @m03x Thank you
th3_maj0r: @georgehotz , do you have any idea how to build an indestructible glass? asking for a friend
Bombapil0t: LUL
NonTrivial778: capitalism
PhysoTronic: georgehotz you dropped ice on floor
forkdb: Please George .. am dying here
whichtom: can a roomba eat ice
chocblade: thats why you will never have a girl friend
st47ik: robot racism cmonBruh
M03x: Modern problems requires modern solutions
Venald: Do you want to become a pro in graphics programming, font-end, back-end, computational programming?
nso1995: My apartment is too big for my roomba
M03x: MrDestructoid what u said homie ??
mathieu_696: TriHard
Ant__K: cmonBruh
quickfloor: Did you watch Logan Paul Fight ???
Bombapil0t: cmonBruh
quickfloor: that was crazy
shaymin_fakezz: MrDestructoid chu mean?
chocblade: thats cause you will never have a girl friend
th3_maj0r: @georgehotz , do you have any idea how to build an indestructible glass? asking for a friend
M03x: wtf dude am an A.I cmonBruh
mexeroserisback: Lean PogChamp
shaymin_fakezz: forsenCD
chocblade: thats cause you will never have a girl friend thats cause you will never have a girl friend thats cause you will never have a girl friend thats cause you will never have a girl friend thats cause you will never have a girl friend thats cause you will never have a girl friend thats cause you will never have a girl friend thats cause you will never have a girl friend thats cause you will never have a girl friend thats cause you will never have a girl friend thats cause you will never have a girl f
mindberries: LUL
st47ik: MrDestructoid i am
Venald: th3_maj0r make a glass out of titanium EleGiggle
LainShotcs: LainShotcs subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months!
d4rkvist3r: good morning
quickfloor: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qjfaoe847qQ
st47ik: PogChamp
forkdb: please.. give some lessons... please am dying here to know from you!!
chocblade: omg intelegence af
st47ik: MetaLean
th3_maj0r: You can write it twice if u sub
aa_ato: Noooooooo!
OnlyB1ade: ALL META
robby0313: massive brain 5head
PhysoTronic: meta what?
mirceau: Jordan Peterson
nso1995: Isn't this a drug?
Phucklif3: favorite language?
st47ik: LeanCoq LUL
init2: What's up guys, George. What is that Lean? is it something like Lean Manufacturing?
M03x: i only know one lean TriHard
GGBreach: LeanCock
liqo13: how about prove category theory theorems in lean?
Kuaang: !time
init2: !time
Keyeh: 21st century math OMEGALUL
init2: !uptime
C4TFive: Wheres your double styrofoam cups for the lean?
nso1995: This all seems like mental masturbation
th3_maj0r: lol
d4rkvist3r: lul
st47ik: @init2 time is 09:48
Ant__K: LUL
st47ik: LUL
whichtom: LUL
GGBreach: CamBoy
C4TFive: We ARE the gifts.
Newmankrr: LUL
UniversalGeneve: LUL kekW
yousef19961: Is he using a Mac
Ant__K: start an only fans PogChamp
foxubu: Alex Alex Alex :)
Ricoello: a cam girl that does it for free
init2: @st47ik O, thanks
AdmiraIGoldenRetriever: 4Head Just run ads
NonTrivial778: LULW
C4TFive: George needs to body paint for us
lidermaury: george but you're a millionaire
crazycatz59: who is this man? Does he have a degree in math? This is some upper-level tier stuff
bobsmash: you have to make a amazon gift list :)
nso1995: Show some skin
W1lkins: George has a premium snapchat
st47ik: @init2 ;)
bobsmash: wish list :D
Darkm1ght: @georgehotz i'll donate 1$ i f you take your top off
C4TFive: body paint for subs
d4rkvist3r: i like to keep my money if i can
Santiago_LHC: @crazycatz59 Google George Hotz
init2: @georgehotz Are u a rich?
foxubu: @Darkm1ght I think he will ban you :D
stianz0: you should show some nekid feets
Darkm1ght: @foxubu i hope not i just got here xD
foxubu: :D
iron_lasagna: ever done sql on stream?
Santiago_LHC: TWITCHCOQ
erichzimm: can you do a typing race?
Keyeh: twitch cocc Kreygasm
crazycatz59: @Santiago_LHC it says he attended carnegie for a little bit but it says nothing about how far he went
W1lkins: Where is simple skills Sunday
anup_kodlekere: what are we looking at today?
st47ik: backspace.ai
C4TFive: vscode DansGame
Santiago_LHC: @crazycatz59 Probably doesn't matter
whichtom: university is a scam anyway
Darkm1ght: @crazycatz59 he took some of the math courses and the hardest comp sci courses like operating systems, compilers, etc.
GGBreach: "Category: Basic Programming" I don't understand anything :(.
Santiago_LHC: @GGBreach it's a joke
okeeeeeee: readable nice
Darkm1ght: @crazycatz59 he talks about his education in the podcast with lex fridman
minichota: Why aren't you programming in basic?
st47ik: mostly math 4Head
C4TFive: why is this file so big
init2: O, Pithon, at least something is clean
johnny_thehobo: if you cant write 10k lines of code without googling are you even a programmeR?
init2: *python
C4TFive: this is like some quick js sized files
l_mbert: where do those ideas come from :D
KitsuneMotion: Imagine not using the Superior nano
Keyeh: GAP language? i thought they made clothes
Santiago_LHC: #nanotrolls
KitsuneMotion: lol
st47ik: Kappa
th3_maj0r: qwerty
anup_kodlekere: what do you think bout cybertruck?
callmemod: Qwertyuiop said that.
Santiago_LHC: I name mine "batman"
Keyeh: got it
d4rkvist3r: waht?
minichota: Wait, what is lean
C4TFive: lean looks like a step above brainfuck
syafiqshaary: FBPass
l_mbert: isn't that a ligature for '->'?
minichota: ^
st47ik: unicode 4Head
okeeeeeee: ->
AdmiraIGoldenRetriever: -->
mexeroserisback: latex
liqo13: its in vscode settings to enable ligatures
okeeeeeee: typographic ligature, a combination of two or more letters into a single symbol
Santiago_LHC: ligature is a font thing
C4TFive: ligatures are a font thing, === would look like 3 stacked lines
init2: @liqo13 If I use vim or emacs?
th3_maj0r: really userfriendly to write
foxubu: Alex <3
Santiago_LHC: but you need a font with ligatures. like Fira Code
xxdvxx: hello chat and geohot!
kovu211: ice melts Pog
st47ik: @xxdvxx HeyGuys
syafiqshaary: U still live in glen rock, new jersey?
minichota: Java
Ziv0: jsfuck?
st47ik: its not that long LUL
johnny_thehobo: sorry :(
sadpoopz: what
Keyeh: is this a canadian language?
LikeVatta: Can i learn programming from watching your streams? Are you a professional?
Santiago_LHC: There is a repo on github with all the hello worlds in every language
sirleeroyjenkins: What's up Georgehotz
Danny: hello everyone
fa_k: ???
vloood: is it too late now to say sorry
Iliftmymousealot: trolish language?
Santiago_LHC: @LikeVatta Google George Hotz
l_mbert: does lean have any use cases? or is it just esoteric or something? :D
Iliftmymousealot: seems trolish
fa_k: yung lean
fa_k: in da club
geracao_7a1: @georgehotz where you live? im from brazil
mephisto7777_: mephisto7777_ subscribed with Twitch Prime.
johnny_thehobo: this is the programming language all the rappers use
luxbock: @georgehotz Programming in Lean is written for Lean 2
TokaMakaridze: !location
fa_k: for some morphine
st47ik: Lean is made by Microsoft research
init2: @geracao_7a1 He is from USA
luxbock: you are using Lean 3
forkdb: How do you know all these?
Bombapil0t: TriHard
mephisto7777_: @georgehotz legend :D
st47ik: LUL
okeeeeeee: LUL
Bombapil0t: basic programming
不好意思: LUL
mexeroserisback: LUL
th3_maj0r: amazing
octwopus: LUL
NilsIRL: LUL
fa_k: LUL
sadpoopz: we are in for a journey LUL
luxbock: you want: https://leanprover.github.io/theorem_proving_in_lean/
sirleeroyjenkins: sippin the lean
Serbius: why dont you just use python NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
NilsIRL: @Serbius python 2 or 3?
luxbock: then you are out of luck unfortunately
NilsIRL: @Serbius same problem LUL
Protoxus: Hello there
l_mbert: I like obscure languages lol
LikeVatta: Can i learn anything here? I mean i know shit all about programming.
Newmankrr: just a slow one Kappa
minichota: why not just use brainfuck
lemonsauc3: somebody get this man some tea!
r00ky: Just use the correct interface....
Ziv0: do it using Python 1.6
Serbius: @NilsIRL "hello world gives problem in python" LUL
Iliftmymousealot: lean does Seen obscure
nawi_ii: Why not use an older version of Lean then?
LikeVatta: I know nothing about programming, is this a good stream to learn programming?
Vjasal: @georgehotz have you ever tried templeos?
st47ik: @LikeVatta no LUL
enzozordan: tea?
Newmankrr: @enzozordan yes
sadpoopz: the language is not suitable for hello worlds
NilsIRL: @Serbius 'print "Hello World!"' != 'print("Hello World")'
l_mbert: true
Azermite: @georgehotz What is the current best programming language to state and prove mathematical theorems ?
LikeVatta: Oh yeah. What site would you recommend?
Santiago_LHC: Don't talk of keyboard
fa_k: actually true
czukuruku: best advice about programming ever
callmemod: Any truers in chat?
st47ik: Kappa /
fa_k: true LULW
johnny_thehobo: not false
CasparBaIT: Yups, im learning about GAns at the moment, pretty damn fun, but yeah only one way,= to do it
lemonsauc3: @LikeVatta Just figure out a problem and solve it in a language you want to learn
l_mbert: !!true
st47ik: not untrue
razr22: @LikeVatta codeacademy, hackerrank
LikeVatta: What's the best language to learn?
Bombapil0t: PogChamp
CasparBaIT: the own u learn
CasparBaIT: *one
sadpoopz: no i did :)
Santiago_LHC: No jailbreak, no self-driving, no keyboard.
st47ik: @LikeVatta python or javascript
th3_maj0r: @trchaosTR you can if u want a time out
Bombapil0t: we are in guys PartyTime
fa_k: PogChamp
lemonsauc3: @LikeVatta Im learning C right meow, but i would reccomend Java or python
LikeVatta: @razr22 best language for a complete nooob?
Iliftmymousealot: lean is a perfect language top learn Basic programming concepts Like how to use Stack overflow to automate the programming process
razr22: @LikeVatta python
st47ik: KappaRoss
johnny_thehobo: hes gonna see monkaS
razr22: LUL
BlLL: LUL
anup_kodlekere: lol
lemonsauc3: lmfao
Newmankrr: LUL
knight69gamer: monkaS
th3_maj0r: ahahaha
Azermite: @georgehotz What is the current best programming language to state and prove mathematical theorems ?
KitsuneMotion: lol
mosin_lol: is he usin a mac ?
myasovlavashe: LUL
Darkm1ght: rekt
fa_k: LUL
CasparBaIT: kek
st47ik: @xxdvxx read the bio NotLikeThis
BlLL: very sassy george
l_mbert: yeah, that's mac @mosin_lol
whichtom: coq seemed to be pretty good
death_gadget: Quick someone ask what his favorite Eminem album is.. LUL
chocolatechp: GEORGE! GEORGE!
aa_ato: 😂😂
enzozordan: i'm very interested in that tea
Iliftmymousealot: is coq not cool anymore ?
fa_k: ask if he prefers ass or tiddy
krispeer: hey chat HeyGuys
aa_ato: myTo
Serbius: @georgehotz when will the new song come out?
chocolatechp: 4 spaces is the only way
johnny_thehobo: sorry :(
krispeer: nobody said hi :(
liqo13: @georgehotz any reason u got into coq and lean the past few streams? does this tie in to backspace.ai?
Leith9: hey :)
luxbock: @georgehotz you need to use the IO monad to read files
Ricoello: @krispeer hi :)
resting01: george how do i learn programming, whats the best method?
fa_k: whitespace hell NotLikeThis
whichtom: practice
KingKewpa: by programming
Darkm1ght: @resting01 just program something
aa_ato: lean /^
liqo13: mods?
fa_k: cmonBruu
resting01: im trying to learn python but i get bored really quickly, how do i overcome this?
luxbock: @georgehotz the type checker complains that read_file returns its result inside the IO monad, thus you can't pass that to a function that expects a string, you need to print inside the monad, as you can't unwrap it
voxelfox0125: just relate programming to something you like doing then you will learn passively.
fa_k: cmonBruh
fa_k: M LUL DS
boevsson: @resting01 I mean.. get something interesitng to do with it
Iliftmymousealot: as far as I Unterstand george's Goal is to find a way to Proof that 2 Programms are semantically equal. obviously this semantics Check cant be used for every Programm because of the Halting problem
ytazn: can anyone explain typescript over javascript
DasMastah: 'return' will still wrap it inside the monad
johnny_thehobo: typescript is garbage
l_mbert: ts has types, js doesn't
xxdvxx: why dash dash?It's interesting..
l_mbert: typescript isn't garbage, depends on the project :D
jmc516: Ayy whattup George and chat
l_mbert: whaddup
Protoxus: Protoxus subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 7 months!
01_pollux: i see vim?
resting01: guys, i want to became data scientist, what skills do i need, particularly in banking sphere ?
01_pollux: phython
ytazn: ok so apparently ts on a team, js when solo but it depends
1monkjuice: get your ass to study, learning what to study is also a part of the process
xxdvxx: you see vim in VSCODE
death_gadget: Statistics
ytazn: hey @georgehotz no offense but you are the best one
01_pollux: yeah there is vim emulator is vscode @xxdvxx
abhb09: Hey Geo
01_pollux: does he do ai stuff in stream
01_pollux: work realted stuff?
euranymous: I missed you george
l_mbert: image not able to google if you have a problem, I think I dig that, should try it out myself :D
liqo13: in haskell u use 'return' to wrap something in a monad. maybe theres smth similar in lean?
frkNNv3: imagine using Vim unironically
whichtom: ??
01_pollux: i use vim all day
01_pollux: hey george do u do ai stuff in stream @georgehotz
sk84uhlivin: Hope you're well George :)
chocolatechp: did you go hiking
whichtom: ai is a buzzword that means nothing
Anakronistick: Just came to this stream. Do you dance or show titties? :)
zuqqqqqq: ah i wish i knew lean
ytazn: LUL
boevsson: @whichtom so wise :D
voxelfox0125: @georgehotz have you ever tried to do a CTF?
zuqqqqqq: kevin buzzard is really into it
d4rkvist3r: lol
chocolatechp: he does dance!
zuqqqqqq: any buzzards in the chat? FUNgineer
BlLL: no just change to "just chatting"
day_by_day: yo why are you exploring all these different proof verifiers? is coq shit or what
01_pollux: you should change ur category to science and tech @georgehotz
Keyeh: haskell is mostly wizardry
ytazn: yeah i just looked up monad and i still dont know it seems complicated
DasMastah: Return wraps a pure value into the monad in question.
forkdb: Haskel sounds more like rascal... haha
ytazn: it feels like most named design patterns are fads
xxdvxx: I thought you're writing BASIC Kappa Basic Programming
zuqqqqqq: because he doesn't feel like it
zuqqqqqq: that's the answer to like every question
zuqqqqqq: ever
zuqqqqqq: DatSheffy 7
liqo13: u can combine multiple monads using >>= or the sugared 'do' syntax
ytazn: LUL
HaywoodJabroni: DatSheffy 7
luxbock: @georgehotz I managed to print a file: https://pastebin.com/LhqiyHZH
xxdvxx: @liqo13 DatSheffy 7
liqo13: nope lean does it like haskell too apparently
chocolatechp: your keyboard sounds so good
fobdden_masud: !uptime
zuqqqqqq: not the k word monkaS
HaywoodJabroni: pajaS K word
zuqqqqqq: you're lucky you're a sub
Nnotm: in haskell it would be
Nnotm: if this is like Haskell, return means something completely different from what it means in, say, python
jmc516: Hey @georgehotz how do you come up with your project ideas?
ytazn: hike sounds awesome great work
1monkjuice: can you zoom in the pdf plox?
Nnotm: still need the colon before the function type
xxdvxx: you can check get_file method for function with arg
liqo13: i was gonna learn agda over the holidays but now i might just try lean first
xxdvxx: read_file**
frkNNv3: what is this language for
coilru: dis chat is actually 200iq wtf
xxdvxx: no we're average
zuqqqqqq: @liqo13 do you do math?
liqo13: cs in uni, learn math using wiki
Nnotm: you can only use <- notation with functions that return a io something (or some other monad)
turbo_mack: @Naotm really? how so that only extracts the value from monad (at least in haskell)
zuqqqqqq: seems like most people that are into proof assistants come from cs
Nnotm: turbo_mack yes that's what I meant, perhaps not phrased in a great way
savlon: did u hack playstation
mmi18: should it be programming basics and not basic programming?
Nnotm: turbo_mack I should have said "value" instead of "function"
turbo_mack: ah right... you can use it only within do block yeah but you still need to return / pure value into a monad that is returned from the function
foxubu: Strange syntax
turbo_mack: yeah gotcha
DasMastah: @mmi18 Basic writing, basic cooking, basic carpenting
foxubu: a mix of fortran and R :D
guy_ross: @savlon https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Hotz
brofessorbob: What language is this?
Nnotm: Lean brofessorbob
mmi18: @DasMastah but basis is a language
mmi18: *basic
spanilith: Cheer21
DasMastah: @mmi18 All capitalized, yes
turbo_mack: it looks like haskell with odd syntax to me :P
Keyeh: yeah bro we get it @mmi18
brofessorbob: Thanks Mate!
anthraxvirus322: what are we doing today chat ?
Nnotm: anthraxvirus322 learning lean
spanilith: too early for coding
anthraxvirus322: I see
Nnotm: hm wondering if the default Lean string type is better than Haskell's
turbo_mack: well define better
turbo_mack: in a way type String = [Char] is elegant
brofessorbob: When does it make sense to use this Lean?
turbo_mack: it sux for performance though indeed
luxbock: @georgehotz "Go to definition" should work
Nnotm: turbo_mack it's nice for learning the language but bad for using it I suppose
luxbock: in VSCode
brofessorbob: What extensions ya
turbo_mack: @Nnotm yeah and then you have to choose between Text String and Bytestring all the time :D
Nnotm: yeah
brofessorbob: ya'll use with VSCode
enzozordan: @georgehotz what kind of tea are you drinking?
JohnnyFresh: what is he programming?
Poselsky: functional language? <3
Leith9: LUL
Nnotm: Poselsky yep, theorem proof assistant
Aregos18: SeemsGood
foxubu: RTFM like good old times in the 60ties :D
xxdvxx: same pdf over and over again
shanumbra: xD
Poselsky: @Nnotm you could say that I love haskell, but I wonder if F# is any good. What do you say?
shanumbra: WHAT THE FUCK HE IS DOING
Nnotm: Poselsky don't really know it I'm afraid
syrob2804: sml nj.
enzozordan: lol
death_gadget: Is it .map?
Keyeh: he's learning
xxdvxx: he's learning WOw
RaJpuTsrijaN: no meditation today?
smurfd0: he's a lean mean math machine
PhysoTronic: georgehotz what is your opinion about sites like codewars, hackerrank, leetcode and sites like that? Did you ever use them, do you have any that you like more than others?
Smithygmx: hey
turbo_mack: @Poselsky the biggest advantage of F# is that it's native for .NET so if you need to interop with .NET it'
turbo_mack: s what you want
Bacon4Life_: why did you drop the name "geohot"? All of your stuff is georgehotz nowadays
ekalsuwaidi: true FeelsBadMan
okeeeeeee: Clap
turbo_mack: otherwise it's more like OCaml than haskell... including inpurities and syntax.
st47ik: PogChamp
okeeeeeee: LUL
Serbius: that was so motivational, thank you george
rikvk01: I feel that
W1lkins: so you like those sites then? Kappa
PhysoTronic: LUL
NoMoreDreams21: LUL
01_pollux: what really?
Bacon4Life_: actor/programmer PogChamp
eaterenrgy: @turbo_mack Haskell is a pure language ...
01_pollux: so who are u now?
foxubu: then whos tomcr00se? :D
xxdvxx: why are you eating ice all the time?
st47ik: tomcr00se PogChamp
turbo_mack: @eaterengy Haskell is but F# and OCaml or SML aren't fully
Keyeh: LUL
Serbius: spit some bars
death_gadget: LUL
st47ik: deep
sausainismilka: sup ex-Eminem.
Keyeh: freestyle
Caene: work to live, don't live to work?
johnny_thehobo: it was cold war bcz is cold in russia
01_pollux: did you move into a studio?
st47ik: "seriously" Kappa
l_mbert: just have fun, and f about others opinions. My Key to happiness
tooI: you could be at least lil dicky level Kapp
PhysoTronic: people in highschool usually made fun of people who were into IT so I dont think that is good example Kappa
rudolphdoesgames: ice tea time?
st47ik: LUL
krispeer: :k OWL2019200iq OWL2019200iq OWL2019200iq
Serbius: @georgehotz you should challenge ytcracker to a rap battle
GTozzi: The twitch category "basic programming" triggers me. He's using lean not basic
PhysoTronic: when I said that I will study IT they looked at me like I am biggest idiot in world
RaJpuTsrijaN: meditation is it really helping? started doing it recently.. it just makes me sleepy. Maybe I am doing it wrong.
krispeer: True OWL2019200iq
resting01: how to find something you enjoy if could not do it to this point
Nnotm: Haskell is at least moving towards dependent types slowly
pietoh: Do you consider yourself a savage?
turbo_mack: well very slowly... for dependent types I would recommend looking into idris rather than hs
alajmo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XsiiIa6bs9I
johnny_thehobo: now i know why im single
thuganalyst: There are a lot of things that you can really be into that aren't valuable like bus-ticket collecting. Read some Paul Graham essay about this.
GTozzi: drugs are bad umkay
Nnotm: turbo_mack I just find it fun following the process :)
Santiago_LHC: "most of you here have used...."
rikvk01: lol
tooI: i never tried any drugs in me life
Bacon4Life_: never Kappa
rikvk01: most of you have used LSD,
Caene: "most of you" - Bro, I barely take painkillers.
krispeer: Using it right now KappaWealth
myasovlavashe: Internet PogChamp
thuganalyst: Steve Jobs pulled the mac from the LSD realm
turbo_mack: @Nnotm but if you're into crazy type system stuff check ATS language.. that is crazy sh*t
turbo_mack: namely linear types
krispeer: Reported Kappa
alajmo: haha don't take LSD, it will deconstruct you and maybe you won't have it in you to rebuild yourself
CbsmonkeyTV: did acid twice. 100% opens you to knew thinking
GTozzi: I smoked three LSD marijuanas before this stream
Nnotm: turbo_mack will do
slanthedeceivers: Lol
Azermite: Other than proving theorem can it infer other theorem from them ?
01_pollux: i hear cherry mx brown?
michalmx2: George, you used to be a night person, now you prefer to work in the mornings, why that changed?
PhysoTronic: when are we going to do meditation? do I have time to make tea before we do it
st47ik: how about microdosing PogChamp
Bacon4Life_: erowid PogChamp
dgkng0d: spacex workers use drugs too
khilshot: What do you think about AR?
whichtom: how did it change you geo
GTozzi: It is kinda funny that we are talking about drugs while using a language called "lean"
RaJpuTsrijaN: recent crypto drop, thoughts?
Wnb_Gosu: drug channel
tooI: i watched "Easy Rider" so i basically know everything about LSD KEKW
st47ik: microdosing is trending in silicon valley
KingKewpa: crypto is a scam
RaJpuTsrijaN: no just thoughts
Santiago_LHC: crypto is not a scam. People are a scam
TwitchlerinEfendisi: scams are cryptos
xxdvxx: i'm shilling algorand today
RaJpuTsrijaN: I bought my first ever cryto this week
tooI: is microdosing what sleepless elite does?
KingKewpa: if there is one thing that crypto taught me about real life its that everything is a scam
THATTACHYON: @01_pollux it's HHKB
zuqqqqqq: microdosing LUL
deadpool_reynolds: hacking your brain?
01_pollux: ohh really nice thanks @THATTACHYON
Azermite: what is the best current programming language to state and prove math theorem ?
st47ik: it's so polarizing NotLikeThis
dgkng0d: sorry for asking dumb questions <3
Serbius: imagine needing drugs for programming LUL
turbo_mack: @THATTACHYON the keyboard right? I was thinking that key sound must be HHKB
Vinndy: what's LEAN guys
grabrato: AGI, thoughts?
krispeer: @georgehotz how do you enjoy programming?
Colinmypusse: ur like martin shkreli @georgehotz
Caene: the problem with people, is that you can't trust them - because most people are fucking stupid.
georgehotz: https://github.com/leanprover/lean
tooI: you know Kappa
dgkng0d: are you eating ice
needhugsnotdrugs: @azermite any LUL
Serbius: @Colinmypusse LUL
zuqqqqqq: free shkreli
MrMcaustin1: Thoughts on the cyber truck?
l_mbert: that's why I like this stream, varity :
l_mbert: :) :D
rikvk01: Yes thoughts on cyber truck please
zuqqqqqq: no
zoki_macola: omg a female, i've seen some of then
RaJpuTsrijaN: and the PR setup :')
01_pollux: he probaly hates it @rikvk01
PhysoTronic: rikvk01 wtf is that?
mksdev: Thoughts on the cyber truck?
st47ik: LUL
iPOdk: You just ruined my life as an avocado slicer, what am I suppose to do now?
suteki1: PogChamp
Santiago_LHC: CYBERTRUCK!
death_gadget: It's true
Keyeh: cyber truck is 100% meme
KingKewpa: cybertruck looks like something out of a 60s movies on how they thought the future would look like
needhugsnotdrugs: girl? PogChamp
Caene: worst looking vehicle in history.
MrMcaustin1: Which version of the Cybertruck do you want?
ytazn: 86% of truck owners are stick wielders
dgkng0d: oh that was unexpected
Vinndy: how does one make his girlfriend understand that they like to code on the weekends?
thuganalyst: Low-Poly truck
foxubu: I still wonder how the armored glass test failed. Didn't they really test this?!
rudolphdoesgames: tbh I kinda start to like the cybertruck
iPOdk: It is just rendered in low-poly
Nnotm: from the front is the most flattering angle
Caene: should be pretty easy, with the shape of the vehicle and all.
spanilith: i like it, i dont want to look at F150s being the same for another 25 years
Hunted9000: It looks like something out of Roblox LUL
st47ik: maybe it'll change a bit until 2022 LUL
khilshot: Build one then XD
Ziv0: LUL
Santiago_LHC: People already made that. Look for "Cyber truck mars"
whichtom: ye from the front it looks good, from the side not so much
Nnotm: I feel like the designed is a bit unbalanced in profile, lot more going on near the front than the back
myasovlavashe: Pog
thuganalyst: Some1 Photoshop
needhugsnotdrugs: LUL
tooI: that looks like a perfect battlebots design
zoki_macola: it would be cool if tesla redesigned all of its cars to match that language
eaterenrgy: And there are actual plants on the ground.
Vinndy: do you wanna go to Mars @georgehotz
krispeer: Is that his mom chat?
ytazn: that is not a guy
foxubu: I still wonder how the armored glass test failed. Didn't they really test this?! :D
spanilith: go stay in Amboy and then decide
Colinmypusse: i wanna bang u @georgehotz
DasMastah: But George, it'll be the best hotel on the planet
tooI: jokerd6Coom jokerd6Coom jokerd6Coom jokerd6Coom jokerd6Coom jokerd6Coom
krispeer: Is that his mom chat??
Nnotm: I'd expect the earliest hotels to be 5 star, but might be a while before there's hotels at all
Penguino138: It's his lady friend Alex
Azermite: best drug : getting high of nothing
KingKewpa: it was a stunt to get more publicity
RaJpuTsrijaN: was it wrong glass or PR stunt
piqsoul: Why do I feel like I've stumbled upon a serial killer's stream...and I kinda like it
Sycto: the glass failing either way worked out pretty good for them
BrainRPG: Hello @georgehotz !
Santiago_LHC: It looked way to genuine to be a stunt
DasMastah: The window had dropped down a bit after the sledge hammer hit, so the structural integrity was lost
khilshot: Ever thought about hardware hacking streaming.
foxubu: conspiracy theory about armor glass :D
RaJpuTsrijaN: they gotta have checked it once before
Caene: Elon linked a video of where they stressed the glass, pre-show.
my_curiosity: experimenting with vscode instead of vim?
ytazn: i feel like if you have the balls to try who cares if you mess up
Nnotm: Elon posted on twitter a video of Franz throwing balls at it an hour before the event and the glass not breaking
BrainRPG: @georgehotz have you completed the Natural Number Game?
W1lkins: @georgehotz https://i.imgur.com/nODnKwL.jpg
Colinmypusse: have you ever burned the inside of your dick from peeing too hard monkaS @georgehotz
spanilith: why does the glass have to be armored? its just weird
Caene: The glass was already stressed, that's apparently why it broke so easily on stage.
Infinitelym: how would showing that the glass doesn't work translate to more people wanting to buy it...?
okeeeeeee: in the demo the glass was not fixed in frame, that makes a huge difference
st47ik: @W1lkins that's fast PogChamp
dgkng0d: am i wrong or did you talk with elon about autonomus vehicles
rudolphdoesgames: @W1lkins nice :D
okeeeeeee: its just a shit car, no need to waste a sentence LUL
Serbius: @georgehotz do a drunk programming stream
Santiago_LHC: @Infinitelym Because it went viral and a lot more people end up finding out this thing exists
Caene: @Colinmypusse SeemsGood
foxubu: @W1lkins Beautiful
TheDrewPeacock: mizkifEgg
MatiGoG: pajaW
GTozzi: Can you direct me to books/papers on developing markup languages/typesetting? Historical would help as well @georgehotz
GTozzi: I am a law clerk now, and in the future I'm looking to develop better systems within the field ~~ for document drafting. Because using vim rn is oof given all the pdfs and docx
death_gadget: What happened with the bet between you and Tesla?
Infinitelym: @Santiago_LHC That still doesn't make sense, it literally broke. And it's a car. Logically, you don't buy a car that breaks when a rock is lightly thrown on it
rikvk01: what are you working on?
W1lkins: @georgehotz https://i.imgur.com/nODnKwL.jpg open link SeemsGood
ytazn: @spanilith 43% of guys in the us own guns
Keyeh: @W1lkins nice photoshop bro
rikvk01: Does someone know what he is making?
GTozzi: @W1lkins yeah. fast too
Nnotm: maybe the language has foldl1?
suteki1: PogChamp
ytazn: LUL
Colinmypusse: one time I put a nail in my penis and hit it with a hammer monkaS
whichtom: yo that looks sick
iPOdk: Nooo I was just about to make that PS with you in the front
andrewnakas: Cyber truuuuuck
Nnotm: georgehotz in haskell it uses the first element of the list as initial value
iPOdk: Stupid fast indian PS workers
andrewnakas: Pressurized version incoming
okeeeeeee: i drive in a cyber truck to next bitconnect
Santiago_LHC: @Infinitelym it's still two years away from going in production. Obviously they will fix anything that needs fixing and improve it a lot by the time people can buy it
W1lkins: iPOdk maybe next time
iPOdk: @W1lkins urs was way prettier :p
Serbius: @georgehotz do a stream where you teach a random pleb programming
W1lkins: Mine wasn't even ps Kappa
spanilith: if it can mine bitcoins ill get one
GTozzi: It actually does remind me of NASA's "mars truck" when I see it photoshoped liek that
syrob2804: how do u get up so early?
TwitchlerinEfendisi: cant you just put some info into your description?
swagettiyolonaise69: nobody ever: ... george: let's learn lean
death_gadget: @GTozzi Are you familiar with LaTeX?
Santiago_LHC: @Infinitelym Also, in every other car, the ball would have completely shattered the window. So...
ytazn: gunshot wound mortality rate is only 27%
GTozzi: @death_gadget very
brickvo: anyone know whats hes doing ?
grabrato: Cheer1
Nnotm: is lean evaluation strict or non-strict by default?
spanilith: car glass in the doors is very strong, standard
ytazn: he's building something cool
GTozzi: @death_gadget I am looking ot find information on developing marku, typsetting, etc
whichtom: learning lean
st47ik: @brickvo https://github.com/leanprover/lean
piqsoul: Isn't there a version of the CyberTruck that can go 600 miles on one charge? That's nutty
TwitchlerinEfendisi: we're not supposed to @brickvo
death_gadget: Cool. It sounded like something related to your question... Gotcha
RaJpuTsrijaN: he needs a tilling manager for better efficiency
ytazn: i think the main reason for the cyber truck shape is so it goes farther on once charge
Wnb_Gosu: where are my glasses
GTozzi: @death_gadget very related. thanks
jay_al97: @georgehotz checkout Project Euler. they got really cool math problems
jay_al97: https://projecteuler.net/archives
ytazn: visual studio is op what a beast
acae: i bet u get this question alot, but i'm thinking about learning some programming language, what do u recommend?
st47ik: @ytazn sharp angles aerodynamics are bad, i think the point of the design is to stand out the other trucks
l1ttlemtman: lean or metamath
l1ttlemtman: @acae
whichtom: the point is to look cool
turbo_mack: imo you need 2 more arguments... initial accumulator and list to perform the fold on
ytazn: @st47ik box cars are shaped all flat and smooth
whichtom: it has little function, its just to look cool
whichtom: lol
zuqqqqqq: lol
Nnotm: turbo_mack no initial acc because it's foldl1 instead of faldl
Nnotm: foldl*
zuqqqqqq: foldl1 is canceled
st47ik: teardrop shape is the best aerodynamically speaking SeemsGood
spanilith: alexa order parsley
whichtom: yeah like an airfoil
turbo_mack: ah I see so it can work only on Semigroup, right?
vay_man: hey
guy_ross: woah
Nnotm: turbo_mack well, foldl doesn't even need a Monoid instance, that's fold. foldl1 only works on non-empty lists.
st47ik: mods..
Nnotm: turbo_mack otherwise throws an error
vay_man: hi geo
W1lkins: DansGame
leopp: someone is causing trouble
BrainRPG: @georgehotz , Have you completed the Natural Number Game?
wethenoobs: should i learn angular or react
Vinndy: wait i just realized he's using vscode
huggg_me: wow
Wnb_Gosu: @wethenoobs c
vay_man: react
dpolar: react
ytazn: vue >= react > angular
mkc0de: @georgehotz why not vim?
RaJpuTsrijaN: vim plugin in vscode
wethenoobs: is vue really that good
wethenoobs: ?
Wnb_Gosu: @ytazn true.. vue best
ytazn: depends it's more like a library
wethenoobs: hmm
ytazn: idk tho ive never used it just installed and built
vay_man: I just came have no idea whats going on
foxubu: @mkc0de He's using VSCode with vim extension. Watch him typing carefully
ytazn: no framework decouples you the most tho
smurfd0: did you check on the publications site at leanprover, somoene created a https://github.com/dselsam/certigrad "Bug-free machine learning on stochastic computation graphs"
Vinndy: what are you guys' opinions on the matrix movies? just watched the 3 this weekend
vay_man: it finr
whichtom: i only remember the first
vay_man: fine*
whichtom: its pretty good
whichtom: bruh
death_gadget: You're so edgy...
death_gadget: Kappa
crazycatz59: !uptime
Vinndy: somone ban @huggg_me lol
K177Music: cmonBruh tf
K177Music: cmonBruh cmonBruh cmonBruh cmonBruh cmonBruh cmonBruh cmonBruh cmonBruh cmonBruh cmonBruh
RaJpuTsrijaN: I like how fast he can absorb the documentation. That's a skill I want.
K177Music: i see it cmonBruh
st47ik: mods NotLikeThis
vay_man: @RaJpuTsrijaN yes
K177Music: LULW
01_pollux: u need a mod @georgehotz
MichaelA1337: Hey
shanumbra: @RaJpuTsrijaN INDIAN ?
K177Music: me TriHard
Vinndy: are there no mods in chat?
MichaelA1337: Me
K177Music: jk don't mod me, i'll abuse it :)
01_pollux: not me
guy_ross: mee
RaJpuTsrijaN: @shanumbra namaste
dpolar: do you have followers only mod on ?
knilecrack: noone
vruthlessv: noice
W1lkins: I am a mod :)
spanilith: !
SonOfSatan: i'd be a mod but i'm lazy
shanumbra: @RaJpuTsrijaN NAMASTE
alienware997: Here!
MichaelA1337: I will subscribe with twitch prime next month when I can
liiiiiig0: LUL
MrMcaustin1: Just subbed for you
whichtom: >1 month sub
K177Music: LUL
GTozzi: LOL
foxubu: 11 Month
vruthlessv: OMEGALUL
Serbius: select a random pleb BibleThump BibleThump
death_gadget: Channel classes have been established. LUL
khilshot: yo
K177Music: PAY 4 MOD KEKW
TwitchlerinEfendisi: look at the perks!
GTozzi: Hey, I have been a loyal creeper
K177Music: PAY 4 MOD LUL
vay_man: congrates
ytazn: LUL
guy_ross: im only top gifter for subs *cough cough*
MichaelA1337: What are you making?
K177Music: capitalism KKona
vay_man: all
W1lkins: alienware PogChamp
GTozzi: that's fair
MrMcaustin1: Party250 Just subbed and donated bits for you bb
thes1nbad: congratz boyz
ytazn: subscriber supremacy
K177Music: LOL
dgkng0d: i want to sub bot turkish financial currency dead
Prince0mar: <message deleted>
ytazn: LUL
K177Music: lmao
MrMcaustin1: Walked away when I donated rip
K177Music: 5Head marketing
piqsoul: What is happening I'm scaed
piqsoul: scared
spanilith: pay to win
sanaki13: what chair brand is this?
GTozzi: If I subscribe can I become your ambassador?
K177Music: george is having a mental breakdown :(
Inconnu_xD: this mod thingy is so cheap it should be 399
K177Music: LOL
Serbius: @MrMcaustin1 donating to a millionaire LUL
TwitchlerinEfendisi: who is gonna be the first banned person by a mod?
ukluke13: strong flow
piqsoul: can literally hear him peeing thats a good mic holy
death_gadget: For all the none mods you can go get a job slicing avocados now
K177Music: washed his hands PogChamp
Vinndy: what about the company structure in which you pay your clients tho? @georgehotz
JdPaulBlart: can someone ban me
piqsoul: didnt even wash hands
MichaelA1337: what is he making?
K177Music: dicks
Vinndy: cooking without washing his hands LUL
foxubu: @Vinndy We do not talk about Comma here ;)
Colinmypusse: i want to be a mod :(
K177Music: D:
TwitchlerinEfendisi: washing hands in 2019 WutFace
tris790: D:
K177Music: wtf D:
JdPaulBlart: bruh tthis man is already micromanaging the chat
piqsoul: who tf washes there hands anymore guys
JdPaulBlart: smh
piqsoul: ther
Vinndy: @foxubu it was not about comma, it was about the other day's talk about how companies should pay people he was using drawio
GTozzi: yeah
K177Music: yes cmonBruh
whichtom: yes
K177Music: hades cmonBruh
GTozzi: 1 person imo
piqsoul: That's for sure multiple people
Colinmypusse: multiple people
piqsoul: people are fucking clowns
Colinmypusse: cmonBruh TriHard
GTozzi: Fucking clowns are people
death_gadget: 1 person
01_pollux: she didnt finisht the tea
K177Music: longest porn intro LUL
ekalsuwaidi: i lost Kreygasm
W1lkins: It's just Twitch TV :)
01_pollux: uhhh finish that tea lady
K177Music: porn intro talking about the n word LUL
MichaelA1337: no Im a highschool kid :(
knilecrack: ahahahahahh
duzy: goe is a chad lowkey
whichtom: what
K177Music: 5Head fucks a milf
Zmrdus: ok
piqsoul: go make a sausage
MrMcaustin1: @georgehotz I just give you 250 bits love me!
Serbius: @georgehotz unmod all and make ai to do modding for you
Colinmypusse: I want to fuck ur wife mr hotz @georgehotz
dgkng0d: he banned me too for asking dumb questions and he is right i really asked dumb questions im sorry george :(
Vinndy: ban them from the matrix PogChamp
GTozzi: My real life identity is on that penis
K177Music: PogChamp mod inc
01_pollux: finish that tea lady
K177Music: smh these mods are communist :(
K177Music: they abusing their powers :(
knilecrack: ban is for people as well
piqsoul: wait is this pornhub
dgkng0d: im sorry please forgive me
GTozzi: sorry to ask again -- Can you direct me to books, papers, anything on developing markup languages/typesetting? Historical would help as well @georgehotz
blizz191: l0l
K177Music: they type /ban :(
GTozzi: sad face
Serbius: mod me im german
Inconnu_xD: Mazi Nods Kappa
Sheggellz: I guess I'm on wrong website now :EWA:DAEWD
MichaelA1337: what are you making @georgehotz ?
MrMcaustin1: Cheer250 heres another 250 bits for you bb
Colinmypusse: georgeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
K177Music: PogChamp new moderator inc
K177Music: LOOL
K177Music: LUL
BrainRPG: @georgehotz can you explain how you can prove properties of code in other languages using Lean?
death_gadget: LUL
blizz191: SELLING MODS
minichota: why is mod so far away
Vinndy: PAY2WIN LUL
knilecrack: rofl
foxubu: MaxLOL
dgkng0d: Can mods unban Kappa
K177Music: perfect heirachy LUL
GTozzi: So it was a yes
knilecrack: G IZ A HOOKER
MichaelA1337: Lol
death_gadget: You need to buy a VVIP ticket for a million dollars
knilecrack: twitch hooker
MrMcaustin1: I'll donate more bits once I get a job. Just for you daddy
ProfessorMagikarp0: $5 mod LUL
TwitchlerinEfendisi: you can buy mod rights thats good
jay_al97: @georgehotz do project Elumer https://ubuntu.com/download/server/thank-you?version=18.04.3&architecture=amd64
Sheggellz: Pay2win was good @Vinndy
1monkjuice: id vote for you
MichaelA1337: ill vote for you in 2024
TwitchlerinEfendisi: just make an auction for it
MrMcaustin1: @jay_al97 Wrong link buddy
K177Music: this porn intro is long af
zoki_macola: there is some action
piqsoul: hotz2024
TwitchlerinEfendisi: more you pay more you get
jay_al97: lol
K177Music: skip to the good stuff
MichaelA1337: this is a good programming stream LUL
mexeroserisback: this is the longest erotic movie intro ever
K177Music: basic programming *
GTozzi: GTozzi subscribed at Tier 1.
K177Music: new moderator PogChamp
beaverater: Proud of my boy George for finding a woman that is shorter than he is.
Vinndy: did your girlfriend become your girlfriend by subscribing? @georgehotz
K177Music: a tier 1 sub PogChamp
Aerdayne: wiped off LUL
death_gadget: Did they just say TOR pasta?
gouvernatorn: @mexeroserisback hahahaha
MrMcaustin1: ty @GTozzi for subbing
scsf25: damn george your sister kinda cute ngl
K177Music: KKona
RaJpuTsrijaN: i can't concentrate now :')
blizz191: im hungry now
dgkng0d: @MrMcaustin1 hello new mod congratulations
nic0latesla: your mom is really hot
GTozzi: I accept your nomination as ambassador to the EU. I look forward to testifying against you in front of congress
MrMcaustin1: Thank you @dgkng0d
death_gadget: I'd get down on some of that
khilshot: Uber eats?
piqsoul: I wonder if his girlfriend is a mod
knilecrack: only if she donates 250 bits
piqsoul: ^
K177Music: ^
Serbius: i wonder if his girlfriend is an ai
piqsoul: ^^^^^
khilshot: How long you have been in relationship with her btw?
smurfd0: there is root pasta aswell
MrMcaustin1: @knilecrack *500 bits ;)
GTozzi: Is there a link to a lean project homepage or something?
lightofhel1: @georgehotz how did u find a girlfriend? CoolStoryBob
dgkng0d: if i 500 bits will he unban me
MichaelA1337: what are you working on? @georgehotz
dgkng0d: donate i mean
Vinndy: i'm starting to think that girlfriend questions are going end up the same way as keyboard questions did
foxubu: @dgkng0d You are not banned
piqsoul: did someone say keyboard questions?
dgkng0d: my other acc banned by king george hotz and i created new acc for apology
knilecrack: @MrMcaustin1 she is a GF she gets for half the price
foxubu: Ah I see
knilecrack: I assume 1000bits to for unban
MrMcaustin1: @dgkng0d avoiding a ban is sketchy
dgkng0d: Maybe we can talk offstream haha
death_gadget: You know you average like 3-4x more viewers than all the other streamers that code.
foxubu: MaxLOL
death_gadget: We want more Geo streams!!!
beaverater: Please ban me. I don't care.
khilshot: Do you hate java?
knilecrack: @RaJpuTsrijaN nah that food delivery has to count for something
geobitz: woah toxic
swsh: @georgehotz If you haven't got enough MetaMath, have you heard of MetaMetaTheory https://uniformal.github.io/? NotLikeThis
knilecrack: I need to get bigger screen I can't see shit
GTozzi: Wait, lean is for "building mathematical libraries" what does that mean
GTozzi: Is this for constructing models for referencing?
piqsoul: Other programming streamers don't have as much variety as george
d4rkvist3r: well mods doing there jobs
MrMcaustin1: @RaJpuTsrijaN George does what he wants to do
foxubu: Mods retire rogue replicants :D
l33tkr3w: l33tkr3w subscribed at Tier 1.
Serbius: NAZI MODS DansGame DansGame DansGame
Vinndy: the thing about other programming streamers is that it's like comparing shroud to other fps players might not always be about skill difference but definitely about potential
RaJpuTsrijaN: this is really strict out here
piqsoul: chewing ice is bad for yo teeth
death_gadget: Act up and you get that BAN HAMMER!!
euranymous: I was about to say chew ice
euranymous: LUL
euranymous: Free burgers for subscribers
gouvernatorn: it's getting hot in here PopCorn
PhysoTronic: how does your teeth dont hurt from chewing ice ?
foxubu: @MrMcaustin1 Don't ban ppl for outing wishes :)
MrMcaustin1: Never banned
K177Music: you gotta buy water to make ice though
GTozzi: The milk lobby tricking you into buying more cow lactate
MrMcaustin1: But I understand
MDSZilla: Do you really have to buy it? I always just borrow some water Kappa
bsx1123: When are we gonne play twichtactoe?
foxubu: Nice
piqsoul: Big Brain Move: Buy milk and freeze it and then chew that
gouvernatorn: @gtozzi damn straight
K177Music: true yoink the water from the water fountain TriHard
Vinndy: ice milk 5Head
RaJpuTsrijaN: @piqsoul dairy is bad
dgkng0d: @piqsoul and get sick
piqsoul: lol
piqsoul: ice milk
voxelfox0125: @georgehotz When you code in different languages what is your method of relating their unique styles (syntax, keyword,etc)?
piqsoul: almond milk @RaJpuTsrijaN
RaJpuTsrijaN: that could work
Vinndy: guys at what age do you start to like coffee serious question
abk467: never @Vinndy
sirleeroyjenkins: What kind of keyboard
l33tkr3w: I drank coffee as a kid, but only got into hard as an adult
dgkng0d: @Vinndy im 18 still can't drink cofee
piqsoul: I don't answer serious questions
Infinitelym: @dgkng0d why not?
BrutalCSkAKAN: Hey, are you that famous guy from Instagram
KingKewpa: i drink coffee to fit in, it does nothing for me and it taste awful
l33tkr3w: That he is
GTozzi: It's spelled covfefe
l33tkr3w: Iphone cracker extraordinaire
smurfd0: they have a bunch of more imports
dgkng0d: @Infinitelym in turkey we drink turkish cofee and it taste like shit
death_gadget: Doesn't that mean it can only be called from the module it's defined it?
Vinndy: @KingKewpa been there done that
Wnb_Gosu: @georgehotz I love your "google search by image" software SeemsGood
RaJpuTsrijaN: tuesday is my data structures exam.. maybe geo can teach that just suggesting xd
piqsoul: covfefe is my favorite drink
Infinitelym: @dgkng0d i see
GTozzi: They say chewing on ice covfefe is bad for your teeth
K177Music: lmao
dgkng0d: @georgehotz when you say google search my google asistant started holly crap
K177Music: LOL
RaJpuTsrijaN: stack,queue, ll, tree, graph basics
RaJpuTsrijaN: hash
Wnb_Gosu: HAHAHAHAHA
knilecrack: like you care G
MDSZilla: LUL
K177Music: R OMEGALUL LLED
GTozzi: xd it is. I come from like 3 generations of dentists
piqsoul: LADIES AND GENTLEMEN....WE GOT HIM
spanilith: chewing on crystals
Vinndy: you should stop reading chat you bit the bait @georgehotz
Wnb_Gosu: now ur going to die
liiiiiig0: LUL
spanilith: fatal
teerv: amenia monkaS
K177Music: im gonna have to sue you now :( you broke my teeth
KingKewpa: imagine googling a health condition
PhysoTronic: You have Pica Kappa
MDSZilla: This post is by people who want you to buy milk dont listen to it
K177Music: i started chewing ice after george taught me :(
l33tkr3w: WebMD diagnosis.
PhysoTronic: you are sick, go see doctor LUL
W1lkins: pagophagia PogChamp
knilecrack: YOu have money you can buy new teeth
Caene: You have Pica LUL
foxubu: When google says you have cancer MaxLOL
K177Music: ????????????
liiiiiig0: ??
K177Music: "if you see me chewing ice I won't do it"
prafaeltsantos: fck the rules eat ice
K177Music: wut LUL
spanilith: really the first time you googled that?
piqsoul: can we get a !chewIce command
RaJpuTsrijaN: but it doesn't make any sense
spanilith: haha
MrMcaustin1: WebMD
GTozzi: That should be an emote
Infinitelym: if (chewing_ice): dont()
PhysoTronic: now you must put into your bio that you have Pica Kappa
BrutalCSkAKAN: What about chewing on lollipops??
dgkng0d: letz chew milk
KingKewpa: googles health condition > "chewing ice gives you cancer" 4Head
W1lkins: few bags of ice daily LUL
K177Music: monkaS
whichtom: a few bags wtf
piqsoul: holy shit a few BAGS
Ziv0: monkaS
MDSZilla: A few bags Bruh
K177Music: LOL
Caene: LUL
dpolar: LUL
whichtom: what the fuck
K177Music: chewing ice forums LUL
JIMMY906: lmao
Ziv0: wtf LUL
spanilith: this is how you get addicted
Caene: Oh God... LUL
PhysoTronic: wow, what a website LUL
MichaelA1337: LUL
Vinndy: who even BUYS bags of ice? LOL
foxubu: Holy God
Wnb_Gosu: feelsbadman
khilshot: You can't be always right George. ;-)
spanilith: wormholing it
GTozzi: Hi... my name is George... I am an ice chewer
K177Music: i mean theres a community for pretty much everything LUL
tommy_clash: 4Head
swsh: those ice junkies WutFace
dgkng0d: ice addicteds
MrMcaustin1: lel
alienware997: This is pure gold!
piqsoul: "Yeah, I fuck 3 -4 bags of ice a day"
foxubu: Next subreddit incoming
KingKewpa: looks like ice chewers intervention
PhysoTronic: hahah "my parents wont let me chew ice"
PhysoTronic: LUL
eazyxlan: hey whats keyboard are you using lel
piqsoul: ^^^
smurfd0: whats their bottom line, "i ate ice from the urinal..." :P
K177Music: "it tastes good"
K177Music: lmao
W1lkins: atkins diet plan, chew ice SeemsGood
GTozzi: Out on these streets S-ing D for some bags of ice
XiaoLongBao: because it hurts
foxubu: @eazyxlan Damn you are a subscriber lol
piqsoul: HE NEEDS SOME MILK
K177Music: LOL
RaJpuTsrijaN: check this https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/a4icck/today_i_learned_that_craving_and_chewing_ice_is/
eazyxlan: eazyxlan subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Wnb_Gosu: HAHAHAH
swsh: Do Nice Not Ice!
W1lkins: 2009, he's probably dead now :(
eazyxlan: Kappa
GTozzi: Drink milk, kids. Just say NO to ice
Vinndy: this is exactly from when the internet used to be good
piqsoul: CHEW BONES SUCK MARROW
Wnb_Gosu: 2 days later, George asking for ice in Mc Donald's
spanilith: hang out and chew ice bro
knilecrack: look at him in 5min
K177Music: 😡 damn right
K177Music: fix up your iron deficiency 😡
MDSZilla: Its time I bought me a Ice Machine
K177Music: cmonBruh HESBACK
K177Music: cmonBruh tf
knilecrack: broooo
knilecrack: ahahahahahahahahahahahaha
Ziv0: LUL
MichaelA1337: LUL LUL
liiiiiig0: LUL
abk467: fixing anemia. what a productive stream
XiaoLongBao: ye
W1lkins: where are the mods
W1lkins: slow af
l33tkr3w: LOL, fastest diagnosis ever
knilecrack: ahahahahaha
piqsoul: just inject ice straight into your blood stream easy clap
GTozzi: TwitchMD
kmem: hi hi
a_tr_i: hi guys
khilshot: You can't be always right.
Vinndy: guys let's mark November 24th as the day george started to go sober
W1lkins: I chew ice in liquid form by just drinking it, works way easier
JIMMY906: phew
W1lkins: we've saved him PogChamp
GTozzi: what an emtional rollercoaster
piqsoul: dodged a bullet
MDSZilla: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4813453/ chew this instead
spanilith: BlessRNG
KingKewpa: this chat 200iq once again
JIMMY906: im so sorry :(
eazyxlan: get a whole food vitamin if you want maximum vitamin efficiency
SupaDeviserr: just do some crack, its healthier
GTozzi: o no dis bad
piqsoul: you first have to admit that you have a problem
abk467: NotLikeThis
voxelfox0125: That way worse
MichaelA1337: no
W1lkins: Removed
Vinndy: going from solid to gas PogChamp
piqsoul: lsd tho
MDSZilla: Salvadora persica chewing stick is what you need
alexbos99: raw eggs is where its at
GTozzi: vape the multi vits
Kataphracto: HeyGuys
Wnb_Gosu: @georgehotz mmmm https://ibb.co/jyHHHp0
l33tkr3w: Have you ever suffered from substance abuse?
piqsoul: chew the multi vitamins
khilshot: Eat spinach?
swsh: vapor is just ice in gas form
eazyxlan: I tried vaping and coding and my lung collapsed
ProfessorMagikarp0: lung crystals > chewing ice :)
piqsoul: define suffer
eazyxlan: 0/10
RaJpuTsrijaN: just YOLO dude
liiiiiig0: "yssNO"
l33tkr3w: Got caught up and effected your life in a negative way.
GTozzi: He suffered from years of ice chewing abuse
l33tkr3w: Doent have to be great
MDSZilla: Google Why Vaping is bad and then you might not vape either LUL
Kataphracto: crack and code?
MDSZilla: Everything has its good and bad sides so yeahhhhhh.....
piqsoul: 9/10 dentists agree
piqsoul: the one dentist loves ice chewing
Qrutzarn: how about cocaine?
impact_FWT: whats your keyboard please dont timeout me its the 10th time today
GTozzi: It's a slippery sloop. sad
XiaoLongBao: yeah, that's the danger of it
MDSZilla: Chew Miswak
Vinndy: i laugh every time i hear ice chewers
RaJpuTsrijaN: maybe chew something else
eazyxlan: hhkb @impact_FWT i think
GTozzi: danger is alluring
ProfessorMagikarp0: someone get george an MTV intervention for ice chewing Kappa
piqsoul: chewing ice leads to cocaine
baxteriia: honestly just strarted listening
XiaoLongBao: yeah, you have to be very cautious when chewing ice
baxteriia: is he talking about coke
RaJpuTsrijaN: chew silicon
GTozzi: I started will cool spring water, and now I go threw 15 McDonald's cups of ice a day
v4ltres: is chewing ice some weird slang for doing coke?
GTozzi: large cuts
coilru: what about lean
MrTriharder: @georgehotz what’s the point of not allowing twitch vods for non subs when everything is available on YouTube? Please answer
knilecrack: that is not good
d4rkvist3r: deep true shit
knilecrack: What if you want to be an asshole ?
Iliftmymousealot: deep
piqsoul: I didn't know twitch had a rehab section
Ziv0: LUL
alexbos99: dlnt you dare!
GTozzi: So true. Also, ask does anything they say make sense not high
Vinndy: don't copyright strike the comma archive on youtube for the love of god
MDSZilla: What's better than Coke? Streaming Basic Programming with pure passion <3
Iliftmymousealot: coke helps with coding
revenantrazer: do you smoke wed regularly?
Wnb_Gosu: ResidentSleeper drug channel
d4rkvist3r: weed is the best
swsh: @georgehotz Check out MetaMetaTheory language https://uniformal.github.io/
l33tkr3w: coke helps with coding? I doubt that.
RaJpuTsrijaN: anything overdoing is bad..
alienware997: A room full of Kratom-People
GTozzi: Do you have any thoughts on the Apple v. Oracle API court battle @georgehotz
MrTriharder: But drugs help lower blood pressure @georgehotz
Mariosavitch: coke helps with everything
eazyxlan: have you ever tried adderal and redbull..could really bring up your lines per minute
piqsoul: unless its ice chewing
MDSZilla: MrTriharder they also help lower your brain cells LUL
GTozzi: excuse me
GTozzi: google
hardtarget4: adderall is a scam
eazyxlan: adderall is pharmacy grade meth
l33tkr3w: Amphetamine salt
RaJpuTsrijaN: when we gonna see a stream on DApps
Iliftmymousealot: uv radiation to the forehead is even better than coke.
whichtom: lmao
Vinndy: do people do drugs at def con
r00ky: Just do w/e you want until you can't
piqsoul: hahahaahah
Wnb_Gosu: @georgehotz Change channel category to Drugs
JIMMY906: LUL
coilru: @hardtarget4 how do you know that
Iliftmymousealot: https://rs.io/
liiiiiig0: LUL LMAO
Iliftmymousealot: best blog
piqsoul: Hi George
GTozzi: Isn't the difference between Addy and Meth literally 1 hydrogen molecule
l33tkr3w: WTF, ir leds into his eyes? Commence aiming remote at face.
cerrad1234: @georgehotz what do u think about openshift?
piqsoul: Distraction is the worst drug of them all
codevisionary: ^
l33tkr3w: George, can you explain what your goal is with this project?
RaJpuTsrijaN: is meditation helping you in any way?
eazyxlan: yeah its missing a hydroxl group in its atomic structure i think
Iliftmymousealot: headspace inc
gouvernatorn: there is no goal
foxubu: The goal is learning
GTozzi: headspace lul
l33tkr3w: Meditate? Thats what I call smoke time.
Wnb_Gosu: xD
MDSZilla: Ehh why does it say backspace.ai is not a secure website WutFace
Iliftmymousealot: focus on your breathing
gouvernatorn: the goal is to not have a goal
RaJpuTsrijaN: does it really help though?
MrTriharder: @georgehotz I am from India. I’ll teach you the ways. Say Om 3 times slowly
Wnb_Gosu: #hacked
piqsoul: Todays stream is sponsored by headspace
BrainRPG: @georgehotz How would you prove properties about code in C using Lean?
donats27: Hey George, do you need some Mobile Developer?
OnlyB1ade: What is poppin
dpolar: just not forcing https. https://backspace.ai/ :)
eazyxlan: drugs, we're on them!
r00ky: The solution is: make it work!
piqsoul: someone ban @Colinmypusse
Ant__K: 4Head
ProfessorMagikarp0: sam harris mediation Kreygasm
alexbos99: yer killing me with this stuff
RaJpuTsrijaN: guys for real, does it help? meditation
hardtarget4: nah, it's a scam
l33tkr3w: Seems like high functioning anxiety. Thats my problem.
alexbos99: only if you chew ice
MrTriharder: Meditation help control body fluids gachiBASS
Ant__K: gachiHYPER
piqsoul: Meditation is hard tbh
beninr1: Java or python guys ?
a_tr_i: python
Ant__K: PogChampC
Iliftmymousealot: is headspace pro worth it?
Level_002: !uptime
Ant__K: FeelsBadMan
alexbos99: did you go outside to hve your chew fix ?
MrTriharder: So he’s just gonna leave us here and enjoy
piqsoul: He went outside so no one would see him chew his ice
Vinndy: do you ever fear time @georgehotz
KingKewpa: is he having his ice withdrawal?
zoki_macola: try chemical programming xD
MDSZilla: order some tea
death_gadget: You take the ice away a productivity goes to shit. LUL
r00ky: Prophet BJ > meditation
MrTriharder: @georgehotz my meditation time is the same time as when I’m trying to sleep. Will it work ?
liiiiiig0: we need meditation emote
foogs_: lmao
tychus07: what is happening
codevisionary: LUL
Vinndy: LUL
Qrutzarn: Are you participating in the no nut november CHALLENGE?
knilecrack: what's going on ?
foogs_: this is the best stream ive seen so far on sunday, been following for about 4 weeks.
GTozzi: bro he wants to chew ice so bad right now
MrTriharder: @georgehotz say it with me. Oooooooooooooooom
alexbos99: googles got it's meditation widget
knilecrack: ahahahahaha
subconix: Is meditation a scam?
freecodyx: this is depressing
Iliftmymousealot: nooo
l33tkr3w: Burger fixed the issue
Vinndy: imagine him having TTS for donations while he meditates
codevisionary: https://clips.twitch.tv/BlushingTrustworthyCormorantPipeHype
RaJpuTsrijaN: burger >>> meditation Hence proved
l33tkr3w: Yessssss, excellent clip.
MrTriharder: HeyGuys Alex
piqsoul: Can't meditate while a burger is near by
piqsoul: just like you can
GTozzi: Hope that burger is well defrosted
ikrillz: why no sauce tho?
subconix: Just develop a program to automate meditation LUL
John_DiResta: Is there a bed in the kitchen?
RaJpuTsrijaN: need the neurallink i guess
alienware997: @gtozzi dekarlEss
MrTriharder: @georgehotz a stream where Alex does the whole coding part SwiftRage
l33tkr3w: Does she know how to code?
GTozzi: lmao
zoki_macola: https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1571066105000678
subconix: The ice pellets are Kreygasm
khilshot: Do you ever eat fruits?
piqsoul: Does Alex chew ice as well?
yodiggity4739: is that a real life female
MrTriharder: @georgehotz make her do hello world SwiftRage
dgkng0d: do you like coca cola or pepsi ?
l33tkr3w: Pepsi
BrainRPG: @georgehotz is Lean faster than MetaMath?
khilshot: Yesss teach her how to code and stream it.
shissle: how i get a notification when youre streaming?
Iliftmymousealot: george do you cut out sugar from your diegt?
Iliftmymousealot: *diet
khilshot: "TEaching my gf how to code"
Wnb_Gosu: @georgehotz hamburger is bad too
RaJpuTsrijaN: whats your wpm?
MDSZilla: Hey maybe instead of chewing on ice you start chewing on fruits instead that would be healthy
kmem: should you consume lean? @georgehotz
mightysOckerpunch: The answer is: OF COURSE
smurfd0: they have some under publications, and there are some forks aswell
swsh: tutorial is a documentation
BrainRPG: @georgehotz Why would someone prefer Lean over MetaMath or Coq?
voxelfox0125: Is this the first time you tried to code in lean ?
mazsociety: chewing tar instead of ice might have better health benefits
GTozzi: They developers seemed pretty open about documentation being an ongoing thing
yodiggity4739: should I use lean? No
Iliftmymousealot: from what I can tell lean looks a bit trolish to me...
GTozzi: opening of their pdf manual
nic0latesla: chicken?????
Wnb_Gosu: @georgehotz https://healthyeating.sfgate.com/bad-effects-burgers-11402.html
subconix: Yea there is a lot of pure nonsense in regards to random languages, and obscure CS bullshit.
karl_mundt: bon appetite
ven_ox: HeyGuys
kranos_tv: hello mr hotz how it be gud today
EnjoyToLive: well well well
Wnb_Gosu: xD
liiiiiig0: LUL
foxubu: @Wnb_Gosu MaxLOL
Wnb_Gosu: I tried
GTozzi: It's the cabbage lobby along with the milk lobby
bigduddas: squadW
yodiggity4739: red meat helps lower blood pressure
MDSZilla: Well there are vegan burgers too apparently
EnjoyToLive: the guy who's scared of leadcoder
swsh: dude speaks good things about Lean https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dp-mQ3HxgDE
mightysOckerpunch: Meat burgers are shit for your health, vegan burgers are shit for your health
Iliftmymousealot: did george get the hello world lean program running?
GTozzi: Admission is always the hardest step so sad
kranos_tv: george do you ever do 1337code?
OnlyB1ade: of what
MrTriharder: Weed lowers blood pressure the best
OnlyB1ade: Krakom
khilshot: i like bananas.
codevisionary: bullshit lol
BrainRPG: @georgehotz Why would someone prefer MetaMath over Coq/Lean?
GTozzi: @MrTriharder Psychoactive cannabis definitely does not lower blood pressure.
codevisionary: it makes it higher.
Wnb_Gosu: Your keyboard smells on burger now
Sanneck: bigger font size pls
MrTriharder: But I feel calm and low :)
yodiggity4739: my dad ate a lot of hamburgers and his blood pressure is 0 now
EnjoyToLive: btw the offer still on
1monkjuice: cannabis is magic, sometimes it will lower your blood pressure and sometimes make it higher
MrTriharder: LUL
codevisionary: that's the problem @1monkjuice , it's unpredictable
LikeVatta: What exactly are you doing here?
swsh: it Lean's do syntax is like haskell, there should be >>= operator
mosin_lol: what do you think abour macbook pro 16 " ?
GTozzi: I'm still confused about the intended use for lean is
thundershots999: There is nothing in the world more helpless and irresponsible and depraved than a man in the depths of an ice binge.
codevisionary: LUL wtf lul
khilshot: What's the highest level math you have learned?
tris790: true != false @khilshot :)
Iliftmymousealot: category theory Kappa
mosin_lol: i acutally dont know if razor is more worth than a macbook ..
codevisionary: lean has a weird fucking syntax
thundershots999: Your camera is doing weird focusing
alexlucas_: y o
Aerdayne: forsenS
codevisionary: yeah your cam can't decide whether it's light or dark in the background
xxdvxx: can I shill coin?
codevisionary: it just keeps pulsating
foogs_: Mmmmh
El1T3MaN: F E M A L E PogU
smurfd0: heh the := reminds me of pascal
Iliftmymousealot: best way to get rid of an addiction is to replace it with another more severe addiction
LikeVatta: Is Python 3 different?
swsh: := is a walrus operator
LikeVatta: Guys help please.
whichtom: different to what
xxdvxx: what do you mean? @LikeVatta
LikeVatta: Pyhton alone.
whichtom: ??
LikeVatta: Is there a Python 123?
whichtom: do you mean compared to 2?
LikeVatta: Like that?
xxdvxx: Yeah a little different
raven_ao: thats lean
LikeVatta: Best one to learn?
xxdvxx: 3
whichtom: 3
raven_ao: 1
LikeVatta: All right. Thanks guys.
LikeVatta: I'll go with one.
raven_ao: xd
xxdvxx: Nice @LikeVatta
LikeVatta: Sorry 3
foti_kasparov: Python 3 is a tragedy to humanity says George himself
LikeVatta: i think i will go with 3
xxdvxx: Python 1 is not dead yet.
directrix13: learn this 1 <===
vicrl_: and yet he uses it :o
LikeVatta: It's a tragedy? Then which one?
GTozzi: GTozzi is gifting 5 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
GTozzi: GTozzi gifted a Tier 1 sub to prafaeltsantos!
GTozzi: GTozzi gifted a Tier 1 sub to forkdb!
GTozzi: GTozzi gifted a Tier 1 sub to brisingr1031!
GTozzi: GTozzi gifted a Tier 1 sub to st47ik!
GTozzi: GTozzi gifted a Tier 1 sub to Vjasal!
whichtom: damn son
crazycatz59: ?????
stefanoz45: lol
OnlyB1ade: why
bsx1123: wow
Mariosavitch: python 2 is ass
MrMcaustin1: gg GTozzi
directrix13: meh 3 is ok
EnjoyToLive: and I didn't get anything Kappa
that_turns_me_on: obscure lang sunday? go learn rust instead of this garbo
LikeVatta: I will go with 3. I want to learn some stuff.
Mariosavitch: you dont like printing('like this')?
directrix13: but so was 2
yaus_baus: what gorg code?
LikeVatta: Maybe I just might learn something.
electro_y0: PogU
GTozzi: inb4 threee of them spam the n word
GTozzi: jk
directrix13: if they're going to break shit they should have got rid of the GIL
alienware997: alienware997 extended their Tier 1 subscription through January!
foti_kasparov: Dude if you're a beginner i guess you won't notice any difference
that_turns_me_on: ^
foti_kasparov: Learn something new and useful
0TestUser: grill Kreygasm
natty__gamer: Thanks to you I got to jailbreak my ps3 and host challenge lobbies on mw2. Made good money for my age at the time. Thanks ghotz
that_turns_me_on: oh boy
yaus_baus: damn george tall
that_turns_me_on: tall manlet Kappa
yaus_baus: basketball player?
that_turns_me_on: king of manlets
directrix13: learn ACL2, worship parentheses
Iliftmymousealot: what?
dgkng0d: i still can't understand why dont use metric system
that_turns_me_on: blame murica
foti_kasparov: Where's your tea?
Iliftmymousealot: what does augur say?
EnjoyToLive: i mean what is special about you? you are not helping viewers by answering their questions also you're boring. BUT WHY ALL THIS VIEWS
GTozzi: That is why I only incest in bitcoin
Anarhi99: !keyboard
GTozzi: inVEST
GTozzi: Vest
that_turns_me_on: GTozzi cmonBruh
that_turns_me_on: GTozzi 🚓
GTozzi: the c is right next tot he v guys
that_turns_me_on: sure
that_turns_me_on: calling the cops on your rn
GTozzi: feelsfatfingerman
that_turns_me_on: yo'rue done for, kiddo
Iliftmymousealot: EnjoyToLive who do you mean?
d4rkvist3r: lul
Iliftmymousealot: you mean george?
yaus_baus: george copping cyber truck?
that_turns_me_on: EnjoyToLive imagine not knowing who geohotz is
foti_kasparov: Listen to Gorillaz
Iliftmymousealot: i think he is not answering all of our questions bc they are mostly pretty irrelevant to the streams content
foti_kasparov: Some nice tunes
codevisionary: thank you for hanging out with us George
quickfloor: @georgehotz I WATCHED FOUR ADS IN YOUR STREAM TODAY
quickfloor: we hate ads
dgkng0d: then sub
codevisionary: I would sub but I just subbed to two other people before this stream lol
alienware997: dekarlTOS
codevisionary: I'm broker than a joke
l33tkr3w: Better code some more cash.
quickfloor: i have a broken heart
foti_kasparov: People are full of sh*t sometimes
KNOOKEL_HEAD: i like this song
d4rkvist3r: focus dude
dgkng0d: i like chill songs too but not lofi shit
quickfloor: is george 100% focused or 90% ?
that_turns_me_on: 10%
zuqqqqqq: 10%
xxdvxx: 10%
that_turns_me_on: ayyyy
quickfloor: Wow 10 is really bad
codevisionary: he's using 1.4% of his brain capacity right now
that_turns_me_on: has geohotz ever touched Rust before?
zuqqqqqq: @quickfloor no, we're chilling
codevisionary: he needs tea
that_turns_me_on: heard people say its like c but better
quickfloor: never seen george drink black tea . always green
GTozzi: I love c/c
xxdvxx: better c is c
zuqqqqqq: just wait for c 30
Anarhi99: what was the shortcut to google the selected word?
zuqqqqqq: it's gonna be lit
quickfloor: cool because george hate C
that_turns_me_on: lol
that_turns_me_on: just wait for c (insert version here)
codevisionary: https://clips.twitch.tv/TransparentTangentialSkirretPipeHype
GTozzi: D-- is where the future of the industry is heading
that_turns_me_on: sounds just like people that cant wait for the year of the linux desktop LOL
quickfloor: i think he is tired
GTozzi: ouch
GTozzi: never looked at Go
that_turns_me_on: go is nice
xxdvxx: I think rust is D-- george
foti_kasparov: The more you live. the more you learn that you know nothing
GTozzi: I've been told by teachers they more are preferring it as an introductory language
evokee_: Go is WayTooDank, BTW what are you tryung to do ?
that_turns_me_on: tell them to use Go as an introductory lang instead
quickfloor: Teachers are scam
zuqqqqqq: ^
zuqqqqqq: down with education
that_turns_me_on: modern education
that_turns_me_on: is a scam
swsh: I found this haskell metamath verifier http://home.solcon.nl/mklooster/repos/hmm/
zuqqqqqq: school = child abuse
GTozzi: I think I might have struck a nerve here
zuqqqqqq: fight me
whichtom: i agree modern education is a scam
whichtom: learn everything online
GTozzi: critroleTravis critroleTravis
quickfloor: F colleges , that's right
that_turns_me_on: true that. my father learned about house insulation online and is now making bank off of that
zuqqqqqq: as george once said
zuqqqqqq: you wanna have potential and then not contribute
zuqqqqqq: that's funny
that_turns_me_on: contribute to what?..
d4rkvist3r: fuck college is a mind game get your degree!
vay_man: hi again
zuqqqqqq: the world
that_turns_me_on: thats a big statement
yaus_baus: tldr be a NEET
that_turns_me_on: yea just be a neet and be ded inside
that_turns_me_on: neet purge 2020?
dgkng0d: i am going to sleep good luck george and have fun chat
zuqqqqqq: @that_turns_me_on yeah he then kind of started crying
that_turns_me_on: zuqqqqqq oof, when did that happen
zuqqqqqq: some time ago
zuqqqqqq: but today is chill stream
zuqqqqqq: :^)
that_turns_me_on: that quote actually hits hard when you add "the world" to it
that_turns_me_on: FeelsWeirdMan
yaus_baus: TheOffice
Ziv0: LUL
GTozzi: NEET that's a new term for me
that_turns_me_on: LUL
whichtom: LUL
yaus_baus: @GTozzi u must be new here
yaus_baus: this is aspiring neet chat
zuqqqqqq: @GTozzi that makes me want to call you the b work
zuqqqqqq: word*
swsh: @georgehotz haskell parser http://home.solcon.nl/mklooster/repos/hmm/
zuqqqqqq: (boomer)
GTozzi: I prefer lubbard
GTozzi: ty
that_turns_me_on: bitch?
yaus_baus: here we go
Rtc_ti5: 2
zuqqqqqq: @yaus_baus .
KNOOKEL_HEAD: is the stream buffering for anyone else ?
that_turns_me_on: just you
whichtom: fuck their track
GTozzi: bro what did I do? All I did was say teachers are using Go more frequently to teach comp sci to kids
rafaill: hello George :)
GTozzi: lmao
yaus_baus: neet = enlightenment
zuqqqqqq: @GTozzi it's an old topic
phelipe3: hey george... have you ever tried brave browser?
vay_man: hi from India
d4rkvist3r: LOOOOL
39tjx: What are the best service language to learn right now?
that_turns_me_on: interesting song name xd
that_turns_me_on: 39tjx Go
that_turns_me_on: the only good thing about go right now are the gopher things
svada324: nice doomer music
39tjx: What about Clojure and Rust?
yaus_baus: 1 hour of Metamath Doomer Music Playlist
that_turns_me_on: the worker things that are offered by googles default lib i believe. theyre nice
cnovacost: wich vs code theme are you using
subconix: Angst
Legardovia: Legardovia subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Xingjuice: @GTozzi Is go actually popular? I only ever hear about it on reddit
that_turns_me_on: rust is basically c , if you want maximum efficienty then sure
that_turns_me_on: go isnt popular, no. but its gaining traction especially in server space
dyslexicat: SourPls
that_turns_me_on: devops like it
GTozzi: @Xingjuice It seems to be largely used in academia only from my understanding. And inside google obviously
39tjx: Rust is a language that seems to be growing in marketshare over the past couple of years, but I don't see nearly as much growth as with Go.
coilru: @georgehotz did you consider "Holy C" for an obscure language sunday Kappa ?
that_turns_me_on: coilru LMAO
Xingjuice: @that_turns_me_on You think learning it now would put someone ahead of the curve in terms of future job prospects?
GTozzi: @Xingjuice Literally the only people I know that legit use it work for google
pedrosantos867: song name?
zuqqqqqq: ipfs is written in go
zuqqqqqq: right?
xxdvxx: right @zuqqqqqq
Xingjuice: @zuqqqqqq so is docker
that_turns_me_on: Xingjuice idk about the future honestly. right now i havent seen many job offerings that specifically want golang, its kind of optional here and there
39tjx: Clojure is supposed to be the highest paying server language to develop at the moment.
foti_kasparov: @pedrosantos867 Camping in Alaska - I wanna kicklflip in the sunset and disappear
DGOMS: Hello @georgehotz wonder what you would recommend in terms of language to learn to someone who will soon enter the work market, thank you for your time!
Xingjuice: @GTozzi Hmm, I'm slightly adverse to it because of that quote from Rob Pike.
saintmthw: hi can you make the text bigger im blind
zuqqqqqq: @DGOMS Lean
KNOOKEL_HEAD: you dont even know what language to pick and you are soon gonna enter the work market good one LUL
Xingjuice: @that_turns_me_on That's what I've noticed as well
GTozzi: @Xingjuice Not familiar with it
xxdvxx: @DGOMS python for sure
DGOMS: Not like what lang to pick but what to really dive into
yaus_baus: CSS
thezilion: k
brickvo: css ResidentSleeper
brickvo: jk
Wnb_Gosu: sorry I was not here, I went for some Ice @georgehotz
foti_kasparov: assembly
coilru: @DGOMS im not a programmer, but isnt that dependant on your goals, like what do you want to do
Xingjuice: @GTozzi "The key point here is our programmers are Googlers, they’re not researchers. They’re typically, fairly young, fresh out of school, probably learned Java, maybe learned C or C , probably learned Python. They’re not capable of understanding a brilliant language but we want to use them to build good software. So, the language that we give them has to be easy for them to understand and easy to adopt." - Rob Pike
marsroger44: what editor is that
GTozzi: ew I fell you
KNOOKEL_HEAD: Java is the lamest
foti_kasparov: This band is a gem
that_turns_me_on: Xingjuice job offers that specifically list golang as a primary lang will usually want you to know server-side meaning youll need to know docker/kubernetes or web so youd need to know js and a js framework, probably one of the grand trio
DGOMS: @coilru I'm still in uni, but I'm trying to start to learn things on the side, you know later it will be better
Xingjuice: @georgehotz yeah
Xingjuice: @georgehotz with regards to Golanngs creation
that_turns_me_on: coilru kind of, yes. but once you learn one mainstream language you will be able to learn any language afterwards so it doesnt matter that much
Xingjuice: Golang's*
yaus_baus: tfw geroge is a programming language influencer
GTozzi: The thing about Golang for me has always been why would I use it over Python, C, or C . I've yet to find a satisfying answer .
svada324: googler gang :)
that_turns_me_on: honestly dont know what would be a good lang for starters: something simple like golang or python or something more difficult like say c ?
GTozzi: Pyhton is the best first language imo
RaJpuTsrijaN: invest in typescript may yield good roi
39tjx: Is Rust lame?
Xingjuice: @GTozzi Right, that's been my question about using go as well.
that_turns_me_on: if you learn c wouldnt that be ultimately better since youd also know how to manage memory?
KNOOKEL_HEAD: Python - slow / C unpleasant to work with
that_turns_me_on: c is hard, yes but
Wnb_Gosu: c is easy ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper
that_turns_me_on: hard for a beginner
GTozzi: My introduction to programming concepts was with Java, and then a lot of C/C
xxdvxx: We love GO
Xingjuice: @that_turns_me_on I'm still in school so I'm still focusing on learning that trifecta. I was gonna go with node.js since its quite popular where I live
coilru: why start from something as hard as c, from what i researched python is the optimal language to start with
swsh: easiest first time language is Wolfram, change my mind
GTozzi: That compared to kids now learning with Python. It's SO much easier for them
that_turns_me_on: Xingjuice good choice if you want a job. which js framework do you like the most?
KNOOKEL_HEAD: what do you think about rust george
that_turns_me_on: ^
RaJpuTsrijaN: I liked C a lot when I first started programmig.. .
GTozzi: I love C
that_turns_me_on: c is fun until you start creating something big..
Xingjuice: @coilru isn't it a bit counter productive in the long run to go with a dynamically typed language first?
rudolphdoesgames: making a linux bootable usb, really want to try linux out
coilru: @Xingjuice im the wrong person to ask that, if you think so maybe it is
that_turns_me_on: Xingjuice bro, he probably doesnt know what that is lol
that_turns_me_on: it honestly doesnt matter
GTozzi: We can all agree the best FIRST language is easly Pascal
foti_kasparov: Use Linux on a Virtual Machine
GTozzi: come on ppl
that_turns_me_on: learn general shit - data structures and design patterns
ReiRip: what is this programming language?
Xingjuice: @that_turns_me_on I haven't really dug into any thing since school has been shitting on me but I've started writing a website/web app with vue.js for frontend and node.js for backend
that_turns_me_on: those will be applicable to every other lang
l33tkr3w: Could always install the linux subsystem in windows.
Xingjuice: @coilru oh, my bad lol
r3mote: ...
GTozzi: @ReiRip Lean
Xingjuice: @that_turns_me_on vue.js since its quite similar, from what I hear, to react so I need to I can just transfer knowledge that way
swsh: @georgehotz check this out https://github.com/jesse-michael-han/lean-parser-combinators
ReiRip: @GTozzi I heard first time.
Xingjuice: @that_turns_me_on so if* I need to
that_turns_me_on: Xingjuice yeah ive been learning vue for a while then noticed that angular has better default libs, code separation and ts which is similar to c# a bit since i come from a c# background so i switched to that
YouPowerRush: quick 123
that_turns_me_on: vue is just simple
that_turns_me_on: thats why its good to use, especially good for personal projects
GTozzi: @l33tkr3w The subsystem is pretty bad. I tried using it at work beucase I am a bash sycophant. I had a terrible time using it
W1lkins: angular DansGame
Infinitelym: anyone in chat have any good resources for JUnit 4 testing? maybe something that's not necessarily a simple Google search away?
Xingjuice: @that_turns_me_on are you currently employed as a dev?
l33tkr3w: @GTozzi I have not used it much, just ran some penstest tools with it.
that_turns_me_on: yeah im not a fan of angular either but as ive said it has good code separation/abstraction which is like. yeah i know poor abstractions can backfire but still
GTozzi: @l33tkr3w It's an amazing step in the right direction by m$. I ran into a million issues with it
that_turns_me_on: Xingjuice nope, cant even work right now because of health issues. all i can do is sit at home and analyze the market/learn new shit
l33tkr3w: @GTozzi Yeah im sure there are lots of issues. I was just excited when I heard about it, so of course had to try it.
GTozzi: me too
Xingjuice: @that_turns_me_on ah, unfortunate. Hope things get better man
The_Tyrant: thought george with vim
The_Tyrant: only code*
GTozzi: He still uses it
n3ini3a1: basic programming big Kapp
GTozzi: and had a vim plugin
GTozzi: has*
Xingjuice: You can use vim with VSCode
st47ik: @GTozzi thanks :3
GTozzi: @st47ik np <3
shieeeeeeeeet: !uptime
that_turns_me_on: Xingjuice i have a cavernoma in my brain that regularly leaks over my language perception centers on my brain, im waiting to get more tests and probably get a surgery to get rid of that entirely. not fun at all when i read a sentence and midway just cant read or understand text at all, quite terrifying :D
l33tkr3w: That sounds scary as fuck.
that_turns_me_on: at least the operation is easy
swsh: maybe that's better parser combinators implementation https://gist.github.com/gebner/b4c12bf19dfc96abead83c5864c4ef44
Xingjuice: @that_turns_me_on Holy shit dude. I was thinking some kind of accident that required rest for healing. That's on a whole other level.
GTozzi: Even with your hemangioma, you were super quick to catch my typo earlier lol @that_turns_me_on
Xingjuice: @georgehotz how's the vim plugin for vim? I heard it's a bit lacking
that_turns_me_on: yeah my life is basically on hold right now, gotta chill until i get that surgically removed
Xingjuice: the vim plugin for vscode***
that_turns_me_on: GTozzi im not disabled, the leak(s) impede my ability to understand language for like a minute. i lay down and wait until it passes and then i continue as normal
vay_man: I doant het an'y of it
vay_man: get8
l33tkr3w: Mount your monitor on your ceiling.
Xingjuice: @that_turns_me_on so kind of like a brainfart
LikeVatta: @that_turns_me_on wait what do you need to remove surgically?
Xingjuice: just periodic and as a symptom
white_knicker4: hello george
GTozzi: @georgehotz Have you ever played around with VimScript
white_knicker4: Hello I am a n1ggear pls dont ban me I just am black n1ggear fighting for my rights to pick cotton thank you for ur time 77777777777777777777777777777777777 e
LikeVatta: @that_turns_me_on tumor of the brain?
white_knicker4: pls n1ggear me
Xingjuice: lol this guy
LikeVatta: This fucking guy. LOL
that_turns_me_on: LikeVatta a cavernoma. a small clump of blood vessels on my brain that leak because my body couldnt figure out how to properly lay out my vessels for optimal blood flow lol
l33tkr3w: Interesting.
GTozzi: it has to be the same person
xxdvxx: @white_knicker4 interesting..
LikeVatta: How old are you?
GTozzi: rip mods asleep
whichtom: just ignore it
that_turns_me_on: 22
white_knicker4: 22
l33tkr3w: Gotta be between 12-15.
LikeVatta: And you say you have had this problem all your life?
that_turns_me_on: nope
white_knicker4: i am very autistic
vay_man: you code?
white_knicker4: like geohot
white_knicker4: and martin shkreli
codevisionary: lean looks clean, I must add
ReiRip: !uptime
that_turns_me_on: one day i just kinda passed out, had a seizure and got put in a hospital. 5 weeks ago @LikeVatta
vay_man: stfu bro
domas3210: this chat is LUL
anguscupcake: Why do you use a Mac?
l33tkr3w: Was curious myself.
white_knicker4: mac best platform to code on
that_turns_me_on: LikeVatta maybe i had that clump on my brain my entire life, who knows. one days it just decided to start leaking and thats it. now i just have to wait until i get that surgery and my life will continue as normal
GTozzi: I can't stand non unix/unix-like operating systems
Xingjuice: probably because windows is shit for programming and linux is annoying for use
codevisionary: sorry to hear that @that_turns_me_on
that_turns_me_on: anyway im talking offtopic here
Xingjuice: Mac is like the in between
RaJpuTsrijaN: how is linux annoying fo ruse
GTozzi: I mean just having access to a bash shell without jumping through a billion hoops is a damn good reason to not use Windows
LikeVatta: @that_turns_me_on What did the doctors say the best way forward was?
GTozzi: His meditation really worked. Normally he is 90% looking at chat 5% chewing ice 5% coding
Xingjuice: @RaJpuTsrijaN lol how is it annoying for use? In what other OS do you have to configure normal shit that would be standard or have an easy access option in plain sight. I prefer linux to everything else but let's not act like it's perfect.
l33tkr3w: what medication
GOLDSOULTHEORY: ` I can't stand non unix/unix-like operating systems` isnt linux, a Unix-like operating system?
Xingjuice: @GOLDSOULTHEORY windows
swsh: @georgehotz dude, there is a separate lean tutorial for programming, not theorem proving
GTozzi: @GOLDSOULTHEORY https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Unix#/media/File:Unix_history-simple.svg
Xingjuice: @GOLDSOULTHEORY ingore me I think I misread you
GOLDSOULTHEORY: Gtozzi this is nothing new to me but thanks
Hattedmonkey: PogChamp
Hattedmonkey: hi
GTozzi: Idk what you are asking then @GOLDSOULTHEORY
Xingjuice: @GTozzi yeah his post made no sense to me
GOLDSOULTHEORY: Sorry, think i misread your original post now i think :D
GTozzi: I studied environmental science and was a research diver for year. Bugs don't scare me, kid
zuqqqqqq: he almost said it monkaS
matejsninja: :D
W1lkins: ez ban
GOLDSOULTHEORY: rip LUL
Xingjuice: @GTozzi I hate bugs, the
Xingjuice: they're a run on sight for me
zuqqqqqq: bugs DansGame
GTozzi: I hate bug researchers
GTozzi: lol
zuqqqqqq: if i get a bug report
zuqqqqqq: i close it instantly
GTozzi: now that's the quality control I like to hear
Xingjuice: what's he building?
Hattedmonkey: I wish I knew what was going on FeelsBadMan
Hattedmonkey: me small brain
Xingjuice: same dude
GTozzi: aight peace, nerds
GTozzi: gtg
Xingjuice: later
filedescriptor: @roystang what do you mean by "keyboard"?
foti_kasparov: Ofc this is not useful. The goal of the stream is always to make useless stuff
Xingjuice: @filedescriptor "ask about keyboard = timeout"
shirafx: u are doing all of these but I bet you can't make a subprogram that prints Hello World!
xxdvxx: we can't see @georgehotz
FrazLIVE: This doesn't look like the BASIC programming language... 🤔
l33tkr3w: GOTO 1
vay_man: coz u r dum
Xingjuice: lmao
Xingjuice: I knew that was gonna happen
l33tkr3w: Im confused
jmp0ut: hey geohotz ever work on legion lang
aa_ato: Food!
PhysoTronic: did we have meditation?
saintmthw: what are we trying to do today
sirleeroyjenkins: What kind of keyboard u use?
scorpiocyborg: What keyboard u use?
smeoneleeet: keyboard model?
The_Tyrant: is he using python for most codding?
dorkmo: !uptime
sirleeroyjenkins: can you drink the lean as well
euranymous: WHy is the chat so empty today?
The_Tyrant: anu
mondasama: So my question is HOW TO CODE ?
PhysoTronic: they are meditating Kappa
euranymous: @georgehotz chew some ice LUL
PhysoTronic: LUL
The_Tyrant: anyone knows george setup/gear . laptop desktop ?
PhysoTronic: good one euranymous
youseff_my: hii im doin eee and im not good in programming, any suggestion on how to become good in codingg ???/
shirafx: your ps3 jailbreak works fine bro
shirafx: playing uncharted every day
nahamsec: 54 raiders from nahamsec have joined!
euranymous: Bois know tha you gotta put some blind folds on and feel the code
PhysoTronic: we have a raid
The_Tyrant: he using vscode only?
euranymous: @The_Tyrant He can do all that with just VIM
The_Tyrant: but is he is using vscode rigjt
euranymous: yes
Xingjuice: @The_Tyrant VSCode with vim plugin or just vim. Keyboard is HHKB and probably some external monitor
The_Tyrant: ok
sirleeroyjenkins: what language is he coding in is it mexican or something
nahamsec: HeyGuys
euranymous: leeeeeeeeeeeeeerrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrroyyyyyyyyyyyyyy Jeeeeeeeeeeeeeenkkkkkkkkkkkkinsssssssssssssss
nahamsec: nahamsBountyplz
euranymous: nahamsDupsman
The_Tyrant: @xingjuice you know laptop? macbookpro?
Xingjuice: @The_Tyrant I mean... that's really the only option
RaJpuTsrijaN: just let it go
euranymous: @georgehotz Are you into crypto mining?
swsh: you need an instance of has_to_string
aa_ato: Type
getmadbad: Hi, how are you today :) ? Greetings from Germany!
swsh: read about type classes, the same as in haskell
justsmer: !uptime
The_Tyrant: he only uses a macbook pro with a monitor?
swsh: remove lambda
LaheyFPS: :)
leonzera: hey geo
foxubu: :)
halid96: font size too small, isn't ?
foxubu: a bit yes
foxubu: thank you
aa_ato: y
Xingjuice: what kind of parser is this? I was thinking of writing my own for fun but not sure which would be best to implement
Xingjuice: right on lol
PhysoTronic: its time to meditate : D
xxdvxx: meditation
PhysoTronic: we will think about parser
PhysoTronic: and what to do and then do it after good meditation
alycia: ban
xxdvxx: @foxubu
Xingjuice: @georgehotz I'm currently using these for my classes
xxdvxx: Thanks @foxubu.
Xingjuice: @georgehotz apparently they suck ass as far as efficiency since its basically brute force, not sure if that matters
that_turns_me_on: imagine wasting your precious lifetime just to create new accounts and spam the N word in a random twitch channel
that_turns_me_on: kek
Gtxgaming23: @georgehotz can you define heap in a basic general terminology
roystang: i am free
death_gadget: LUL
swsh: just stick to parser monad
mkc0de: what about discord server ?
Tsoding: What is monad?
Tsoding: :(
Xingjuice: not sure if this will be helpful but recursive decent parsing is basically just getting the next token and if its a nonterminal you unget the token and parse until the you reach a rule that handles terminals. Once that rule is parsed the token will be consumed. You do this recursively for all grammar rules in the language. We're doing it in C so it might be much different for this
Tsoding: I have like 8 years of Haskell experience and still don't know what is monad LUL
euranymous: HASKELL MASTER RACEE
death_gadget: It's a word made to confuse people. LUL It feels like functional programmings word for an object.
Xingjuice: @Tsoding what is haskell used for? It seems like an interesting language to use
matejsninja: @Tsoding ^ same question from me, what real-world projects are made with it?
that_turns_me_on: Tsoding LUL
Tsoding: It's a general-purpose language, so you can use it for anything. But it's a pure functional programming language, which means it's really convenient for things that act like a mathematical functions. For example, parsers and compilers. :D
wiseai: Kreygasm :)
roystang: is that a female
Tsoding: You still can use it for pretty much anything, but some things are not really convenient to write in it. For instance, CRUD apps
foxubu: I have mostly seen math and crypto researchers using Haskell ^^
that_turns_me_on: i-is that a.. a female girl?..
that_turns_me_on: HNNG
whichtom: don't be weird man
that_turns_me_on: im joking
that_turns_me_on: thats how people react when they women on streams
death_gadget: Uh oh we have a serious person in the chat
whichtom: lol
that_turns_me_on: see* women
impact_FWT: stop this bullshit and do some react webdev cmon
wiseai: KEKW
takroli3: guys i dont understand anything pls somebody explain
whichtom: didn't we do react last week
matejsninja: @takroli3 we too and geo too
that_turns_me_on: takroli3 stuff and things are happening
impact_FWT: we did it but we need more
takroli3: PogChamp
that_turns_me_on: pogchamp indeed
Tsoding: @that_turns_me_on I remember you ( =_=)
that_turns_me_on: okay.
that_turns_me_on: thats good
ahmed1dev: hey what editor are u using
that_turns_me_on: your memory is working
Keyeh: its vscode bro
ahmed1dev: is that microsoft ide haha?
Doodle_Jump92: it looks like vs code
that_turns_me_on: yes
that_turns_me_on: it is vscod
that_turns_me_on: e
indifferentghost: @takroli3 he's using the esoteric programming language Lean github: leanprover/lean which is designed for Theorem Proving.
mixtape089: Thoughts on cybertruck??
halid96: What programing langs you know mr @georgehotz
that_turns_me_on: no side mirrors lol @mixtape089
foxubu: It is vscoe with vim keybindings for the record
foxubu: vscode*
that_turns_me_on: oh
Sawfare: is the thingy on the left side your bed?
dgkng0d: hi again i guess i fked up my sleep cycle
Adolfich: what and why u doing? @georgehotz bradhiDelirium
twiggy_io: Ah yes instapot
twiggy_io: Is lean just an interpreter for the text editor or?
Xingjuice: its a programming language
twiggy_io: Nope nvm
jtparker: LEAN is a theorem prover by Microsoft Research
rudolphdoesgames: wasnt he banned?
mariusmafius: rip
zeroeagle1: anyone here have to deal with exchange cmdlet or other shitty miicrosoft service?
twiggy_io: Enterprise level yeah
xxdvxx: dont waste your time @georgehotz
that_turns_me_on: nice
Ricoello: test
PhysoTronic: nice
xxdvxx: nice
that_turns_me_on: inb4 half people in chat cant type anymore
youngmarsh: owned
whichtom: nice
64pillars: ez
d4rkvist3r: hi
tornpaperyoyos: WutFace WutFace WutFace WutFace
that_turns_me_on: gg ez no re
Adolfich: lol
apideveloper: hey
tornpaperyoyos: OWL2019200iq
zgamer0123: I already was a follow :D
wiseai: 5Head
d4rkvist3r: remember that story with the room full of assholes?
NLozar22: but don't you think you are alienating new comers?
Xingjuice: @NLozar22 I don't think he cares lol
xxdvxx: no they must wait to speak at least 1 stream
Xingjuice: I mean they can still watch
jtparker: Maybe new followers must solve a simple prove with LEAN :D
matejsninja: @jtparker so chat would be dead :P
that_turns_me_on: jtparker please no
jtparker: :D
Xingjuice: @d4rkvist3r yeah but its only one soo...
d4rkvist3r: xD
euranymous: is true = false?
that_turns_me_on: 🤔
matejsninja: @euranymous yes
Xingjuice: #define true false
zeroeagle1: ^
matejsninja: @euranymous because you assigned false to true
faulpelzz: do we drink tea and learn something?
Vjasal: @GTozzi thanks for sub
mixtape089: Tips on getting started with ml / deep learning?
matejsninja: i think the name of this language is lean beacuse people creating it and using it must take lean first to undrestand it :P
Vjasal: yo, what do i even get sor having a sub in this channel?
swsh: learning language by trial and error LUL
Vjasal: no emotes >:(
128p_: oh boy the hottest streamer in the neighborhood
0_______________________o: so hot Kreygasm
that_turns_me_on: ^ nice nickname
128p_: pretty nice but I think it might get banned someday...
cod4TV: !uptime
swsh: you can't do recursion without meta
0_______________________o: @that_turns_me_on oi bruv. thank you very much VoHiYo
smurfd0: maby your missing some imports?
swsh: you need prove of termination
0_______________________o: @128p_ "it"
Xingjuice: !uptime
cod4TV: why !uptime is not working?
128p_: ban missile incoming...
0_______________________o: @georgehotz whats this verifier going to be used for ?
matejsninja: why is there a error in stmt_to_string function?
whichtom: been up like 3-4hrs
veritasJS: veritasJS subscribed at Tier 1.
veritasJS: hello
whichtom: howdy
0_______________________o: @veritasJS :D
that_turns_me_on: 128p_ wait.. wtf did he get banned for?
Xingjuice: mentioning that company
that_turns_me_on: whats wrong with that..
Xingjuice: I would assume
foxubu: Usually we do not timeout or ban subscribers ...
Xingjuice: who knows then
thuganalyst: Bruh Cybertruck really got 186K orders
that_turns_me_on: i mean the cybertruck is somewhat competitive
that_turns_me_on: in its price range
that_turns_me_on: isnt it?
zeroeagle1: is there any information about the truck aerodynamic profile vs other trucks/
whichtom: not afaik but id be very interested to see it
whichtom: probably wouldnt be too hard to find the rough geometry and run cfd
zeroeagle1: some fanboys discussion https://teslamotorsclub.com/tmc/threads/cybertruck-is-not-aerodynamically-efficient-why-the-shape.174676/
soul_serpent: soul_serpent subscribed with Twitch Prime.
swsh: it can't prove termination, what if list is infinite?
swsh: there is LUL
veritasJS: did you eat dinner
jtparker: Rule 1: The termination checker is always right :D
3ygun: Isn't an infinite list just a stream?
swsh: use naturals for induction, lookup many combinator from the gist
nudax: first time i see you live stream, keep up the good work!
that_turns_me_on: BabyRage nooooo
wiseai: KEKW
komocode_: design a cybertruck in blender
nudax: lean, is it new?
evokee_: simp KEKW
leander_ms: looks complicated af to me
st47ik: @nudax https://github.com/leanprover/lean
jtparker: I guess nat is already proven
nudax: SeemsGood
leander_ms: !uptime
Fr0zenOfficial: @leander_ms 4h38min
Fr0zenOfficial: at least
jtparker: The termination checker will accept inductive types
leander_ms: @Fr0zenOfficial are you like a manual ´bot LUL
jtparker: Or you have to prove it yourself via induction
Fr0zenOfficial: lol no xD
leander_ms: Why is this under basic programming? Is there no advanced programming on twitch
nudax: the syntax :O
swsh: isn't it expects char, but "$." is a string?
matejsninja: l, before?
guy_ross: guy_ross gifted a Tier 1 sub to nudax! They have given 6 Gift Subs in the channel!
nudax: @guy_ross Tack för prenumerationsgåvan!
leander_ms: There is a new sub in the house george
Enoxx__: "basic programming"
matejsninja: maybe this E from basic.lean
foxubu: Someone please gift @swsh a subscription. He deserves it.
swsh: i just compare to haskell, append for lists :: is of type Char -> String -> String, looks weird to me
whichtom: he mentioned it before, it isn't that complex
that_turns_me_on: ya this is quite basic, what do you mean? Kappa
guy_ross: guy_ross gifted a Tier 1 sub to swsh! They have given 7 Gift Subs in the channel!
komocode_: did hotz ever play half-life?
swsh: @guy_ross Thanks for the gift sub!
guy_ross: np
foxubu: @guy_ross Thank for your generosity :)
komocode_: you need to update macos
komocode_: i see a red badge
OnlyB1ade: I am
st47ik: the new half-life also called Alyx Kappa
dorkmo: Corgo1
Iliftmymousealot: 1
anguscupcake: can't wait to fuck with source 2 engine
codevisionary: are we breaking the record for longest geohot stream?
st47ik: don't think so LUL
nudax: i hope so
nudax: :D
Xingjuice: @georgehotz Do you have a plan for what you stream or do you just wind it?
swsh: have you tried single equals = ?
Xingjuice: wing*
dorkmo: Pride1 uni1
dorkmo: Pride1 Party1 uni1 Party1 Pride1
maefff: Hey @georgehotz any tips for a guy who'sin uni right now and would like to work with you in 3 years?
codevisionary: LUL
komocode_: boat with no LTE?
dorkmo: drop out and start a band
whichtom: do projects my dude and have fun
st47ik: Boat with StalLink internet Kappa
st47ik: Starlink*
yaus_baus: bro lets crowd fund a pirate ship
maefff: sounds like a good idea, I like some rock
komocode_: boat on which ocean?
st47ik: LUL
codevisionary: a country sailing LUL
whichtom: an autonomous boat?
slArkBig: Open a casino business in your boat
st47ik: Decentralized country
yaus_baus: decentralized b o a t s
cccnrd: i subbed while u were offline to rewatch u coding react, then remebered the commaai archive yt channel
codevisionary: what does it take to get on this boat?
komocode_: rape
Max__PWR: rape is fine Kappa
maefff: that went in a way that I couldn't predict :o
st47ik: peer to peer laws
knilecrack: :D
komocode_: pirating software?
Max__PWR: MS george eppstein
yaus_baus: hedonistic murder boat
SurfCat: KKona got my vote
Ziv0: LUL
knilecrack: ahahaha
cccnrd: stahp
yaus_baus: all aboard
knilecrack: do we have internet on the boat?
codevisionary: you said "chemical weapons". You've officially activated NSA surveillance on your stream
komocode_: pied piper internet
cvbook: boat2boat protocol
zeroeagle1: any currency?
Ziv0: monkaS
swsh: space boat!
maefff: you need your own navy
OnlyB1ade: yyeeaaaahhhh
Iliftmymousealot: lets go to mars
komocode_: iphone shipments?
wiseai: get a submarine
yaus_baus: neet army on mars
slArkBig: Contact Elon. He will send you to the space
st47ik: backspace.ai is the focus now Kappa
codevisionary: @slArkBig I think him and Elon have a few disagreements
codevisionary: about self-driving vehicle tech. They might not agree on space either
risky_banana: CyberTruck looks awesome, don't @ me
codevisionary: @risky_banana fuck yeah it does
that_turns_me_on: cybertruck is the perfect car to dab on everyone
that_turns_me_on: while blasting synthwave through your open windows
codevisionary: I just love to watch it pull an f150 uphill while the f150 is in full gear tires squealing for help
WrestDota: what ide/text editor is that
guy_ross: vscode
WrestDota: nice ty
nudax: visual studio code
Particle_x: AHHAA
jtparker: I guess you have to prove that your recursion reduces with every step
Sarkin_dota: This looks suspiciously similar to haskell
MrMcaustin1: 257 viewers and chat is dead
swsh: move your window right, can't see the code
vlds: @georgehotz do you use a password manager?
maskerlive: Most of the viewers are just in awe
swsh: or move yourself right :D
whichtom: ye im just chilling and hacking
Sarkin_dota: So what are we doing here today
st47ik: im eating dinner and watching Kappa
maskerlive: @st47ik same haha
Sarkin_dota: "Smooth"?
cybermajestic: hello
Sarkin_dota: LUL
OnlyB1ade: IM back, Any progress??
SurfCat: Yeah were going to space.
that_turns_me_on: SurfCat PogChamp
st47ik: @georgehotz why don't u get a more comfy chair since u sit for hours?
OnlyB1ade: more structured than python or?
deadpool_reynolds: omg.. last time I checked he was with the hello world
swsh: exstatic FP
M03x: !uptime
Anger_LBow: hello everyone. I am new in this channel. Please dont abuse me.
yaus_baus: ok
st47ik: nah chill bro
M03x: what s he doing ?
vlds: @georgehotz do you use a password manager?
TwitchlerinEfendisi: hello guys please dont hate me
M03x: are all Pog coders introverts ? idk are u ?
st47ik: Lean math Kreygasm
Anger_LBow: Oh, you can get abused. You should watch some LoL streams.
OnlyB1ade: what about math
valerinhopandinho: Hello George. Thank you for inspiration.
SurfCat: monkaS
knilecrack: this is a prototype of boat
yaus_baus: dread pirate geoge
Xingjuice: lol makes sense
st47ik: LUL
yaus_baus: free ulbricht
KingKewpa: free shkreli
yaus_baus: inb4 nsa at the door
zeroeagle1: #free
TwitchlerinEfendisi: free everyone
thuganalyst: he was just tryna enlighten the masses
prometheus_six: Alohaaa guys
montecarlo: Kreygasm
movAX13h: is this real?
Ziv0: LUL
yaus_baus: is he just flexing on us
st47ik: Alyx is cool Kappa
JUST_5HEAD: <3
OnlyB1ade: PokCharizard PokCharizard PokCharizard PokShadowmew
Vjasal: why is he kissing his sister DansGame
Bombapil0t: NotLikeThis
wiseai: Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm
montecarlo: DansGame
M03x: cmonBruh
Anger_LBow: i used to be cool. but then i took an arrow to the knee...
danizx2: whattt
montecarlo: is this a adult film set
KingKewpa: i saw this intro in a porn once
gyne: get a room
mephisto7777_: @georgehotz weird flex LUL
danizx2: the hands
TwitchlerinEfendisi: sexual content needs a report
tatted_Schnitzel: is this the safe space?
danizx2: i see u
nic0latesla: i'm hot
M03x: is she his gf ?
montecarlo: she's his sister
danizx2: caution the hands
st47ik: HeyGuys Alyx
danizx2: i see u
wiseai: Kreygasm
valerinhopandinho: What does he program today,
valerinhopandinho: ?
KingKewpa: does she even know how to code?
HotBobby: coolest programming (and nutritional health) stream i've seen on twitch!
movAX13h: "nice colors"
st47ik: MS Lean NotLikeThis
nic0latesla: jailbreak next topic
HotBobby: vitamins!!
death_gadget: Don't chew ice
M03x: @georgehotz u went to university or u are self taught ??
wiseai: KEKW
st47ik: Iced tea for life
tatted_Schnitzel: do you know about "Hello SafeSpace" tho?
dorkmo: essential oil stream
gamozo: Sup Geohot, how've you been?
yaus_baus: the sacred texts
danizx2: what is your girlfriend thinking what the fuck is that
st47ik: LUL
danizx2: xs
danizx2: xd
tatted_Schnitzel: some hard ice in my mouth yummy
knilecrack: internet man :D
firstavegner: is she a computer scientist ?
whichtom: this is definitely legit
yaus_baus: george is a mod on icechewing.com
death_gadget: 75% trolls.. Let's prove it with LEAN
prometheus_six: Leave the people and their ice alone :)))
gamozo: Could just be people with pica
Balthazar_Bratt: ice ice baby
Anger_LBow: its like entries from 2004
gamozo: Esp wit hthe references to starch, which is a common thing for pica
HotBobby: whole bunch of undiagnosted pica on that forum yeah
anguscupcake: george if u tell me what drugs u use I will subscribe
valerinhopandinho: could you share your charisma?
prometheus_six: Long Live the Ice People :))
KingKewpa: ice connoisseurs PogChamp
Bombapil0t: confused now
st47ik: @anguscupcake tea 4Head
knilecrack: y'all crazy
death_gadget: No
yaus_baus: shill ice
st47ik: H2O is schedule 0 drug Kappa
knilecrack: get liquid nitrogen
dvdutch: Did you use bitboards when developing your chess engine? Or 2D arrays?
HotBobby: FDA food code handles ice for drinking yes. not sure if theres a difference if you chew it!!
zeroeagle1: no but it require to be kept in cold condition
prometheus_six: @georgehotz U'll create the next Icetopia? :)))
dvdutch: Imma tell my kids thats michael jackson
yaus_baus: hows gibby lookin
st47ik: LUL
wiseai: NO MORE CODING DansGame ?
knilecrack: wsup with that imma tell my kids thing ?
mlgdotca: his mom milf
st47ik: imma tell my kids george is steve jobs Kappa
dvdutch: Jibby
Bombapil0t: hot sister hotz
crazycatz59: DON'T CALL HIM JIBBY D:
yaus_baus: gibi asmr the fuck lmao
gamozo: Why are hacker chats always so fucking thirsty
dvdutch: Gibby dated Emily Ratajkowski fun fact
prometheus_six: I used to watch Icarly on Nickleodien or something like that
firstavegner: is she his gf or sis ?
thuganalyst: She pronounces GIF with a J
dvdutch: Bro Google "Gibby Emily Ratajkowski"
KingKewpa: @firstavegner both
prometheus_six: Idk,in my country there are different channels
tatted_Schnitzel: obviously sister
yaus_baus: bro
prometheus_six: HOLLY ICE
dvdutch: Told U
prometheus_six: ....
whichtom: what
st47ik: PogChamp
firstavegner: @KingKewpa what the fleck
akaCube: wait what
prometheus_six: ONE LUCKY SON OF A ICE....
wiseai: Kreygasm Kreygasm
yaus_baus: gibby 4 prez
dvdutch: Well puberty tends to make ppl more attractive
SurfCat: "I guess" LUL smooth
prometheus_six: @georgehotz This looks like that "Before&After" thing :)))
gamozo: LOL
HotBobby: first hit for r in geohotz history is recursive descent parser hell yeah
st47ik: 2019 PogChamp
dvdutch: Buy iCarly puts
yaus_baus: the sacred texts
wiseai: NETFLIX
gamozo: What's going on in Delaware?
st47ik: this trend is the US only?
OnlyB1ade: stonks
illdealer: trending on the east side of the states
whichtom: what trend did you look at before? category theory?
prometheus_six: In my country ICarly is on kids tv in kindergarden :)))
death_gadget: The ending was SO bad
M03x: ?
whichtom: yeah that was it
wiseai: nickelodeon is going to be in netflix
akaCube: Most could understand it, but why should we, if it is entertaining as it is?
prometheus_six: Wich Avatar? Kora or Aang?
jluiiizz: Aang of course
draas: james cameron?
voxelfox0125: Avatar the Last Airbender is a fire show
chesssist: jasonrB jasonrQ jasonrQ
nic0latesla: geohot is hot
prometheus_six: Wich Episode?
prometheus_six: Or season :))
TwitchlerinEfendisi: In report screen: Sexually explicit or pornographic content
Nightness25: LUL
prometheus_six: Zuko is a drakee
yaus_baus: george hates chat
gamozo: RIP
gamozo: xD
SurfCat: it's all over pack it up boys LUL
yaus_baus: rip
JUST_5HEAD: Kreygasm I LOST
tazicke11: im first Time în here, wtf is that
3ygun: hit girl ruined our Twitch Chat
3ygun: hot*
SurfCat: :(
TwitchlerinEfendisi: george please don't hate me, you can hate your other viewers
wiseai: NOOOOOOO
HotBobby: thanks for the stream!!!!!!!
dvdutch: Wait demo the parser
prometheus_six: nono
looterjennings: NOOOO
dorkmo: HeyGuys100
piccibrah: this guy fucks Kappa
jluiiizz: Thanks man
NotKarar: Are you sure you don't hate us?
prometheus_six: Ice made u to go :(
yaus_baus: parsers over girls
gamozo: gamozo subscribed at Tier 1.
gamozo: :D
looterjennings: parser > girls
HotBobby: any chance you could tell us the name of th e screen/tmux looking thing in your terminal? would really appreciate it! thanks!
SurfCat: Yeah no girls allowed in this clubhouse Kappa
tazicke11: first Time în here wtf is that
prometheus_six: Hey Geo,wich programming language should i learn for pen testing?
illdealer: HotBobby hes using screen
whichtom: his configs are on his github but they are really old
dvdutch: Is "|" not a bitwise operator in python?
whichtom: yeah it is
lightofhel1: its lean, not a python
dvdutch: Doesn't lean use python
MrKaragoz: I don't think so
dvdutch: Does george prefer yaml to json?
HotBobby: @illdealer didnt know you could have screen put a list of windows / time on the bottom
HotBobby: thank you
data_bAS3: hey man
data_bAS3: what we doing here ?
data_bAS3: vim vs emacs ?
death_gadget: Creating a meta-math parser in LEAN
emilwallin: what is lean
data_bAS3: thnx @death_gadget
data_bAS3: no idea @emilwallin
emilwallin: haha okey, same here
GTozzi: dangg he's still going
th3_maj0r: lean is a programming language
death_gadget: Lean is a functional programming language created for Theorem proving.
MrKaragoz: uptime
GTozzi: Lean is a life style
Piqcyl: Did you ever figure out how to do 2 2 ?
death_gadget: We aren't talking about what you put in your cup. :)
emilwallin: george stop programming math stuff please its boring
MichaelA1337: it's not boring
leander_ms: 2 2 is 4
gamozo: All programming is boring if you find it boring
artyom__chyornyj: how does this guy earn money for living?
data_bAS3: its complicated @MichaelA1337
MichaelA1337: he owns comma ai @artyom__chyornyj
3ygun: how do you google to find the docs for the language "learn"?
data_bAS3: running commaai
sulozor: vs code ? :o
th3_maj0r: it's lean not learn
3ygun: @th3_maj0r thanks NotLikeThis
illdealer: imagine if it was learn, how to learn learn lulz
MichaelA1337: @3ygun https://leanprover.github.io/about/
alycia: what is this useful for? i have no idea what he is doing
valerinhopandinho: I understand nothing
data_bAS3: damn it i wish to code like he's doing :(
MichaelA1337: same
3ygun: Did he talk about why he switch to "lean" over Coq earlier in the stream?
kovu211: Which IDE is this?
illdealer: hes just trying it out
data_bAS3: vscode @illdealer
MichaelA1337: Visual studio code
sulozor: Whats the vim plugin he is using?
illdealer: should be the top vim plugin in vscode
illdealer: dark mode cus hes not a monster
data_bAS3: i thought he is using linux
MichaelA1337: no
data_bAS3: why mac ?
illdealer: data_bAS3 hes rich
whichtom: because windows sucks
MichaelA1337: I don't know
whichtom: and he has a linux VM anyway
data_bAS3: i know many "rich" people using linux
shieeeeeeeeet: is lean a subset of metamath?
death_gadget: In the inductive definition it's the only one that is (list stmt)
artyom__chyornyj: what does it matter about os anyways, he's coding in vs code
swsh: metamath not a programming language
data_bAS3: i guess he was also using ubuntu for some model training ... in one of his videos
W1lkins: sorry
Balthazar_Bratt: magic happened
K0enich: wow
v1ewy: @georgehotz what are you working on?
data_bAS3: LEAN metamath parser
quickfloor: did george sleep last night ?
quickfloor: i think he is sleepless
tooI: he is part of the sleepless elite after all
tooI: jokerd6Gold
swsh: gotta do nat business again to terminate probably
tooI: whats the keyboard meme?
tooI: jokerd6Head
illdealer: its how you get timed out
swsh: in "scope_stm (parser_core n)", n shoud be the length of the scope
swsh: weird
gamozo: ayyy
valerinhopandinho: @swsh what does he programming?
valerinhopandinho: @swsh simple as possible
valerinhopandinho: plssss
swsh: maybe [] case helps
swsh: try mapping over lst, but also including [] case
swsh: @valerinhopandinho He is implementing MetaMath verifier in language called Lean
valerinhopandinho: thank you a lot
ajsimeone: lean back
valerinhopandinho: I'm 22. Is it to late to learn something very difficult? Now I works as data scientist in a bank, but... I want to do something new(
ukluke13: 22 is young af lmao
daydreamix: lmao 22.
valerinhopandinho: work*
barkazzaz: @valerinhopandinho that's a weird flex if I've ever seen one
valerinhopandinho: flex?
ajsimeone: define data scientist
death_gadget: No, it's not to late. It's never "really" too late. But being 22 you have plenty of time to do something new.
ajsimeone: ^
inderspooni: inderspooni subscribed with Twitch Prime.
prvk3: guys i'm almost 24 is it too late for me to become a circus baboon?
ajsimeone: no
prvk3: is lean like haskell?
sippinoonapplejuice: what we coding?
whichtom: i think its similar to haskell
suteki1: FeelsGoodMan
piccibrah: very cool
xrealyy: george do you consider yourself as a genius?
prvk3: i love u george
inderspooni: Hey @georgehotz
wafflesan: why so smart?
whichtom: have a good day dude
dorkmo: Party100
johnykeri: byeeee
risky_banana: What's your favorite EV and why is it the CyberTruck @georgehotz ?
Balthazar_Bratt: thanks for streaming
death_gadget: Been fun as always
johnykeri: thx fr the stream
inderspooni: how long were you at cmu @georgehotz
wafflesan: mac OS so good Kappa
sippinoonapplejuice: do u like apple products more or windows? @georgehotz
illdealer: don't leave us
whichtom: options CMD esc
squishy_swishy_fishy: cmd option esc
illdealer: can't u cmd QQ or something
guy_ross: lol
wafflesan: LUL
death_gadget: I guess the stream continues
swsh: LUL
sippinoonapplejuice: apple os sucks for obs
MichaelA1337: LUL
johnykeri: lol.
piccibrah: lol
wafflesan: catalina??
deadpool_reynolds: RIP macosx
script_sh: nsa streaming
whichtom: try menu bar
Balthazar_Bratt: activity monitor mb
sippinoonapplejuice: cuz apple os sucks
wafflesan: Windows FTW
whichtom: lmao
squishy_swishy_fishy: wut
johnykeri: obs being ninja
wafflesan: finally